Have you any idea
just how much shit
your boy and his mates are in?
Witness says
they were negotiating
with a bunch of sheiks over
what looked like a gold bath.
Gold bath.
Spread the word, Hate 'Em.
The Mad Hatter's Tea Party
will commence tomorrow.
Vic Hill escaped.
Took a guard hostage
and staged a riot.
- When you'd two get out?
- About 37 minutes ago.
What's gotten into you?
He thinks you put
the moves on her.
I am not putting
the moves on Chloe.
Tread carefully.
The posh one's got
a hard on for you.
Of course I take you
seriously, Charlie.
No, look, I... I mean...
that way.
You should be in prison
finishing out
the rest of your sentence.
What the hell have you
gone and done?
I think I should be asking you
the very same question.
My old lady
suppin' a glass of wine
with my old mate.
Very fucking cozy.
Only Vic Hill could think
two friends
having a meal together
needs more explaining
than a bloody jailbreak.
Well, the imagination
doesn't too many fences to leap
before it runs wild,
if you know what I mean.
Just take a breath, Vic.
Lily was arrested last night,
and we thought it best
that she didn't
go back home alone.
Arrested? For what?
It was nothing, you don't
need to worry about it.
No, he needs to know, Lil.
Bob Fink planted a shooter
at the house.
Pinched her
on a false gun charge.
Bob Fink?
Why'd he come through the doors?
I don't know, Vic.
Maybe he thought I had
an ear on the gossip.
This bullion robbery's
got everyone
riled up all over again.
And do you... have an ear
on the gossip, Lil?
15 years later, and you're
still obsessed with the gold.
You haven't even given me a hug.
She's been through the wringer.
She needs your support, mate.
Am I to understand
that you're advising me...
- how to talk to my wife?
- No.
No, not at all, Vic.
I'm just trying to keep
everybody happy.
Then do just that, Norm.
Keep me happy.
Give me a clue.
A whiff to sniff out my pile.
You're chasing shadows, Vic.
- Hate 'Em?
- Vic?
Fancy a stroll?
Nothing like an afternoon
walk to give one clarity.
What do you say, Norman?
That's a quality job
we did on that.
See, this is not a question
about quality, Uncle Dean.
Yeah, more a question
of portability.
You what?
Move around-able-ness?
See, a bath's a bit
difficult to move, innit?
More, we...
gonna need it re-smelted.
Re-smelted?
The fu...
We will do it.
On one condition.
All right.
Who have I gotta
iron out this time?
No, no! Hey, no!
No, no!
No fighting this time,
Billy son.
Just a wee chat.
A wee chat?
Oi, come here. You all right?
I got Norman's message.
Told me Bob Fink
had arrested ya.
Yeah, we've got
bigger problems than Fink
right now, Albert.
Go on.
Your dad's out.
He's out?
What do you mean he's out?
As in out of prison.
Bowling around
as free as a bird.
Busted out with Hate 'Em All
this afternoon.
He's broken out to get the gold.
All roads leave to Rome.
Selfish prick.
We've gotta tell him
we've got it.
No, no, you can't
do that, Albert.
- Why?
- He's not thinking straight.
He'll mess it all up, and
he'll take you down with him.
What you gotta do
is get him off the street,
just get him off the street.
Yeah?
Who's this?
This is Chloe Koen, Mum,
my business associate.
Hey, Mrs. Hill.
It's really nice to meet you.
Since when did you have
a business associate?
Chloe, fill her in. You be nice.
I'm gonna go have
a look for him.
There are only a couple
places that he could be.
So tell me, Chloe...
What exactly is your racket?
Well, I... I'm not sure
what my racket is, Mrs. Hill.
I've just been helping
Albert with some connections
to help move...
The... consignment.
You're too pretty for a fence.
I don't see myself as a fence.
More of a facilitator.
And are you
an effective facilitator?
Heh!
I'd say I was
a work in progress.
And can you actually help
Albert move this consignment,
or are you just
pissing in the wind
like everybody else
in this neighborhood?
I'm doing my best, Mrs. Hill.
Well, I need you
to do better, Chloe.
My family's in trouble.
What are you doing here,
Master Charles?
What are you doing here, Staff?
I attend the manor house
once monthly
to besom out the cobwebs.
"Time will surrender dormant
"so the rainbows of new eras
can emerge.
Despite the hollowness of you."
I think a hot bath
and a change of clothes for you.
I can't have a bath,
my dear friend.
The gold tub is gone.
Long gone.
Gold tub, Master Charles?
It's presently being re-smelted
into a giant, gold,
gleaming bust of Albert Hill
by Uncle Dean and his clan
of gypsy artisans.
What on earth
are you talking about?
Shh. I speak secrets.
To London, Staff.
All this country air
is starting to repair my lungs.
Whoa!
Christ's sake, Dwyer,
is nowhere sacred?
Sorry, sir, it's Bob Fink.
He's become
a full-blown liability.
Shot up a carpark, killing
Father John in the process.
Then takes it upon himself
to pinch Lily Hill
on a trumped up gun charge.
Look... If Fink wants
to piss the day away
chasing B-listers, he can
arrest the family goldfish
for all I care.
He's up to something, sir.
I think that he's got a lead.
You have an entire unit
of the Flying Squad
at your disposal.
Do you need a bigger strap-on
to sort out one problematic
little officer?
No, the strap-on I have
should suffice, sir.
You need to focus your
attention on finding Vic Hill.
If anyone can lead us
to the bullion
and help crack this
investigation, it's him.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Nas, it's Chloe Koen here.
I have a business proposition
that I think
you'll be interested in.
Give me a call back
when you get this message.
Okay, speak soon. Kiss kiss.
To the nearest
public house, Staff.
Absolutely not.
I'm taking you home to sober up.
Well, that is not gonna happen.
I'm gonna...
What do you think you're doing?!
Anon, Staff.
Master Charles!
Get back here immediately!
Here he is.
Lady Carnation, Billy Ayers.
Even more like him up close.
What's this all about?
This is the chat.
I'll, I'll leave youse to it.
I'm, sorry,
but do I know you?
You know of me.
King Royston.
As in my old man?
Heh.
What about him?
I'm afraid I'm the one
that had him done over, lad.
As in... cut to ribbons.
Well, good on you.
I'm sure he had it coming.
Billy! Wait!
So... the truck barrels down
the frog 'n toad...
Hits the spike strip...
Pop pop pop pop pop!
Tires shredded like
cheddar stand at ease...
I run up to the driver
all cock and bulls
when he pulls out a heater.
Sticks dos barrels
right in my boat race...
But I was too quick for him.
I smack the heater
out of his German bands,
swing it around at him,
and he pony traps
in his Alan Wickers.
Look it up on YouTube, mate.
It's all there
in full digital glory.
Can I get a picture with you?
I've never met a real life
gangster before.
Well, now you have.
It's all Dom Perignon
and trips to Rio
from now on, darling.
She's dying, you know.
Shame.
All she wants is a wee word.
Talk about the old times.
No, I know everything
I need to know.
I'll tell the boys
to stop smelting then.
Will I?
Right.
What do you think
she wants to talk about?
How should I know?
Gloat, probably.
Listen, my parents,
however you tell it,
they come out
looking like tossers.
A pair of irresponsible wankers.
Random shag, baby on a doorstep,
and a dead pikey, and she is
the one that offed him.
That's a shit story.
Want to know what I think?
- Here we go.
- I think it suits you.
Having a half-assed
idea of it all.
Yeah, and how's that then?
'Cause as long as you're not
tied to something solid,
Billy Ayers, you can
walk away whenever you like.
After you.
I love what you've done
with the place, doll.
You can move in if you like.
Could do
with a hard man's touch.
Be rude not to.
Well, well, well.
Look what the pussycat
dragged in.
God. Not you again.
Buckle up, Charlie.
You're in for a rough ride.
Very subtle.
There he is.
Albert, my son and heir!
Father.
You know, you're
a resourceful one, you know.
How'd you find us, Albert?
Call it an educated guess.
He's half shot up
your boy, isn't he?
Yeah, the apple does not fall
far from the tree, Hate 'Em.
Ain't that the truth.
Come here, boy. Give me a hug.
Come on, give me a hug.
I feel the strain
of 15 years of loss
in your embrace, boy.
You're half cut.
Well, that is incorrect,
because I am intoxicated
on possibility.
Come here.
Get on down here.
Come on, here, like that.
Now you, come here.
So what's the idea of you
busting out of prison?
You know Mum's worried sick.
Your Mum seems all right
to me, Albert.
In fact, she is
positively made up.
Yeah, well, why don't you
come back to Norman's
and lay low for a little bit?
Lay low? I think not, son.
Myself and Hate 'Em,
we've got things to do.
Is that not right,
my trusty steed?
Right, yeah, our calendar's
are fully booked.
- What things?
- You know.
Pot of gold, end of
the rainbow and all that.
You heard anything about those
chancers that boosted it?
Yeah.
You got your shell-like
close to the wire, right, boy?
I don't know anything.
Probably out of the country
and sold by now, innit?
- No!
- No, I beg to differ.
- No?
- Sold? No.
I beg to differ,
you see, because...
I can smell it. It's close by.
Very close.
Yeah, well, who knows?
You do know you two stand out
like a pair of big bollocks
on the back end
of a very small dog, don't ya?
Why don't you do yourself
a favor
and get your ass
over to Norman's
and give Mum one less thing
to worry about?
Don't make your mum's
worries your own, boy.
You'll never grow up.
Oi, Albert...
Albert, where you going?
Stay, stay! We'll have a shandy.
Flying Squad. Shit.
Mum, I found him.
Where is he? Is he okay?
He's fine. He's at the Spieler.
There's two... two unmarked
outside casing the joint.
Looks like Heavy Mob.
We've gotta get him
out of there now.
- I hope you told him off...
- I did!
Get a load of these two.
I'd go with the one on the left.
She'd eat you alive, mate.
If I ever catch him
snorting bugle
off that bird's tits again,
I'd chop it off and put it
in the mince, I shall.
Dad, we gotta get you
out of here now.
There's plainclothes outside.
You sure, son?
Yes, I'm sure. Come on.
I've got a van running
in the back alley.
Wait for me, wait for me!
Hey, wait for... Oof!
You two look
a little suspicious.
Lurking around
like a couple of pedos.
What you up to then?
I'll tell you what
they're up to, Shell.
They're waiting for us,
aren't you, boys?
No, Dad, hold up.
Slow down, slow down.
Hey, hang on, oi!
- No, no!
- No chance.
Move.
Vic, I think I've been stung.
Me too.
They've dirty, filthy
blow-piped us, Hate 'Em!
They've done me again, Vic!
- Hey!
- Dad, get in the van.
Unh!
Eddie?
Albert?
Sorry.
Unh!
He's touching me,
he's touching me!
Hate 'Em?
Albert? Wait for me!
Vic! Vic! Vic!
You are so naughty!
Jonsey, Jonesy! Isn't that...
Hate 'Em All Henry.
Get off! Move, move!
Vic!
Wait for me.
Too rough, mate!
- Shit!
- Get back in the car.
Fuck!
So... this is what it's come to?
Shot and tied up
by my own family.
What do you expect?
It's the only way we could
get you to listen.
You listen to me, Albert.
You unite right now,
or so help me God,
I will tear you another asshole!
For God's sake, shut up, Victor!
Just shut up!
Leave me alone with
your father, please, Albert.
No, I'm staying here with you.
I need to talk
to your dad alone.
Go on.
Let's hear it, Lily.
I'm all ears.
All I've ever wanted...
is to have you back home.
Don't you understand?
So untie me.
Let me show you
what I can do for my family.
You're bugger-all use to us
in prison, Vic.
So I've been bugger-all
use for 15 years.
- The penny drops.
- I have paid my price.
It is time to collect.
And what about the price
me and Albert have paid?
What about all those years
that boy never had a father?
And I never had a husband?
I'm very sorry about that, Lily.
If you untie me,
I promise you I will
make it up to both of you.
What we are owed
cannot be weighed in gold, Vic.
Do not leave me
tied up in here, Lily Hill!
You will stay in that chair
until you grow a brain
or a conscience, Victor Hill.
I'd be happy with either.
Lily.
Lily!
All right, then.
Let's hear it.
Expect you know
your mummy was a singer.
Romeo and Juliet
it ain't, but...
it has a certain class.
Yeah, well, even a deadbeat
has his moments.
Yes, you probably thought
she was a drunken slut
and he was there
to nick the tour bus?
Well, I may have started
rumors to that effect.
Well, that doesn't
change anything, does it?
He had his warnings.
He knew the stakes.
Marriage promise was struck
when we were still kiddies.
Ask you this, love.
Why do you think he risked
it all that morning?
You must have wondered.
All he had to do was leave
your ma alone for five minutes,
meet me at the altar,
he'd still be alive.
It's okay. That's it, baby.
Drunk, stubborn.
How should I know?
He sent me this.
The night before...
Poetic little bugger,
weren't he?
"I'm sorry, but feck it,
I love her."
That doesn't help.
And it doesn't change anything.
Put down roots. Take a stand.
Take it serious.
All that fairytale bullshit.
It's what got him killed.
Aah!
No. No, you daft twat!
What killed him
was sending a sorry note
to someone who couldn't read!
You bastard!
Well, I stayed here anywhere.
And I tell you, Billy,
it's an easy life.
Satellite telly,
BaByliss foot spa,
and access to every
dreamboat in camp.
But sometimes, Billy,
sometimes...
The hardest thing
is the better thing, you know?
I learned that the same time
as me ABCs.
He made the right choice.
I'm sorry
I buggered it up for him,
and I wanted to say so before...
I don't...
Isn't this lovely, Charlie?
Getting to know each other
a little better
over a bit of raw fish.
What the hell
do you want from me,
you fuckin' lunatic?
You know exactly what I want.
But I'm done asking,
so I'll just let you
volunteer the information
in your own good time.
You'll get nothing from me.
Do you think
your friend Albert Hill
would take the same
punishment for you?
I do. Twice as much.
Well, where is he, Charlie?
You're the one tied up
on the floor
like a beaten dog.
You're the one about to get
each and every one of your teeth
kicked down your noble throat.
And your best pal,
maybe your only pal,
is nowhere to be seen.
You might want to consider
re-buttering your bread mate.
Ahem.
Fair warning, mate.
Things are gonna get a lot worse
before they get better.
God.
- We had him.
- Had?
In the past tense,
as in, "We no longer have him?"
He slipped through the net, sir.
Far be it from me
to draw attention
to the self-evident,
but in this age
of equal opportunities,
I was so very much
looking forward
to proving the naysayers
wrong in my...
recommending a woman
to lead the Flying Squad.
I was the best candidate
for the job.
Well, that's
where we differ, Dwyer.
I think the best candidate
for the job
would be up to the task
of tracking
a stick up artist long past
his sell-by date
and his eight-foot
Neanderthal bushwhacker
without allowing them...
to slip through the net.
I can explain, sir...
One moment, please, Dwyer.
If you don't lock down
Vic Hill, Dwyer, I will.
And then what use
would I have for you?
On it, sir.
Right.
Vic.
You okay?
Having a ball,
thanks for asking.
I feel for you, Vic. Truly.
Heh.
I can't imagine being away
from a... beautiful family
like yours
all those years.
It would've tore me apart.
Every second of every day.
Here.
How long have we known
each other, Norm?
Wow. Heh!
Must gotta be pushing
30 years now.
We kicked in a few doors
back in the day, pal?
More than doors, Vic.
I've let you all down.
I know that now.
I want to make it right.
For Lily.
For Albert.
For you, Norm.
For me?
Well, let's face it.
Things haven't been easy for you
these past 15 years either.
Got left out on your ass
when I got nicked.
I feel responsible for that.
Well...
Hasn't been easy.
Cut me loose, old pal.
Let me make things right.
For all of us.
Well, that gold is...
as much mine as it is anybody's.
Right, Vic?
More than most, Norm.
Be lucky, Vic.
Luck's for losers, Norm.
Listen, I... It's possible
that I've...
been, like...
Keeping you
at arm's length or whatever.
For...
For the wrong reasons.
I'm so used to just...
Move-about-able-ness?
Move-about-able-ness.
Then... maybe we should just
stay put for a bit.
See if it fits.
Yeah.
Your owner's a bugger,
you know that?
Scooter...
I think it's possible
I may have cocked up
in an unprecedented sort of way.
Remind me to apologize
to Chloe and Albert.
If I ever get out of here alive.
Okay, Nas, that's great.
Let me know
your travel arrangements
and we'll work out
all the details.
Okay.
Bye.
Yes!
What are you all excited about?
Nas Stone is coming
to London tomorrow morning.
Is he really?
And we're happy about this why?
He wants the rest
of the gold, Albert.
Like all of the rest of it.
I have to be competitive
with the price.
15% discount
for the bulk purchase.
I hope that's okay, but he says
he'll take all of it.
Yeah, no, that's more than okay.
That is brilliant!
Albert!
Yeah? What's up?
- He's gone.
- What do you mean he's gone?
Your dad, he's gone!
Oof! Unh!
- Shit!
- Unh.
You ever think to use
the zebra crossing?
It might be beneficial
to your health, mate.
Vi?
Bob?
I'll rip your head off!
Put the brakes on, Vic.
You wouldn't want to assault
an officer of the law
on top of everything else
you're up against at the minute.
You ain't the law, Bob.
You never were.
Whether I am or ain't,
it suited you fine once.
15 years I've wondered.
Why? Why'd you do it, Bob?
The gold.
Decent cut earmarked for you.
Why did you rip me off?!
I could pretend it was
the promise of a bigger cut.
I could pretend the badge
was still worth a toss
back then, but you know
the truth, Vic?
They took me out for a pint.
Flying Squad detectives
and brass.
They acted like I was crew.
That simple.
To to you lot,
I was only ever...
Convenient grass.
Why you hassling my family?
Tracking Albert, arresting Lily.
What do you want?
You know what.
Same thing as you.
Nah.
It's more than the gold
isn't it, Bob?
Fact is, it ain't really
the gold you want at all, is it?
Then you tell me, Vic.
What is it?
What is it I want?
Bragging rights.
Pride.
Suck some of that poison
inside of you.
Show 'em all
who the smart one is, right?
I see you.
I put you...
I put you onto the best scores
of your career.
I made Vic Hill. Me!
All you had to do
was just show a little bit
of appreciation.
Aww!
The cold bloody fish
who just wanted a cuddle.
You sold us to the Sweeney
just because
they pretended to like you.
First chance they got,
they heaved you
out of the way and all.
Do you know why,
do you know why?
Enlighten me, Vic.
Because you're a sinister
bollock, a fuck-up merchant
that no one wants at the party.
It's because
you cannot be trusted
with big boys toys.
You're right.
I am a very sad man.
I'm a very lonely man.
Not like you.
Surrounded by
your loving family.
Where are they again?
Some people
just don't appreciate
what they've already got.
They're too blind to see
what's right under their noses.
You know something.
You've got a lead
on the metal, haven't ya?
You've only gotta ask, Vic.
I'll clue you in.
Level playing field.
May the best man win
and all that.
All you've gotta do
is say "please".
Like, you said, pride.
You rob me of mine.
I'll have yours instead.
The gold is mine!
And I will not have some slimy
little two-Bob shit nick it
because nobody ever hugged him!
You don't know, do ya?
You have no clue.
Know what?
Bang.
You hugged your boy lately, Vic?
You think he trusts you
with the big-boy toys?
Albert?