Your dad's out.
Busted out with Hate 'Em All
this afternoon.
He's broken out to get the gold.
Get him off the street.
Just get him off the street.
They've blow-piped us, Hate 'Em.
Well, well, well, look what
the pussycat dragged in.
You'll get nothing from me!
Do you think your friend
Albert Hill
would take the same
punishment for you?
- I do.
- Nas Stone is coming to London.
We're happy about this why?
He wants the rest
of the gold, Albert.
He says he'll take all of it.
Vic?
Bob?
You don't know, do you?
Know what?
Yeah, Bobby Adams' gang.
I knew it. I bloody knew it!
When I bought this place
off Jonesy five years back,
he said, "Tommy,
I've had some dealings"
with a bit of a naughty crew."
"Nasty types," he says.
Used to come down here
for all manner of mischief.
Last year, they
buggered off to Spain.
Let the heat die down
after something big.
Here you go.
Yeah. Yeah, it fits the intel.
Yeah, you did the right thing,
calling this in.
Truth is, I did some homework.
It says, "If no claim is made to
articles found at the property",
ownership rights refer
to the landowner."
- That's me, right?
- Yeah.
That is you indeed, sir.
Give us a hand to bring it up,
will you?
Yeah, all right.
Sir... I found something I think
you should take a look at.
Mornin', pal.
Bit chilly last night?
The shelter's just opened
on Dexter Street.
Weren't much of a queue there
when I went past.
Get a bit of breakfast...
and a shower before
the rush starts.
Here...
Get yourself a bacon roll
and cuppa
before you go back
on the hard stuff.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Vic Hill!
This... is my manor.
And this... is my rubbish.
So piss off.
No sign of him.
Well... well, you just
get back out there, Albert,
and keep looking for him.
Look, I been traipsing
around the neighborhood
looking for him all night, okay?
I got my own shit to deal with.
He's a big boy.
I'm not gonna follow him around
with a mop anymore, all right?
No, that's not okay...
Your father is out there
on the street, on his own,
and he's not safe!
Okay, well, let's say I do
manage to track him down.
Then what, you want me
to dart him again?
Maybe this time
I'll run him over with the van.
Have you considered, just once,
that Dad is not the bloke
you think he is?
He's a selfish prick
that doesn't give a fuck
about either one of us!
Don't worry about it.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
Albert...
Scooter.
If I ever get out of here,
I'm gonna make a few changes.
I'm gonna be more dependable.
You talking to the fairies,
Charlie?
Piss off!
Look here.
There's no need for
that kind of hostility.
This is a good time
of your own making.
I fail to see
how being snatched,
chained up, and beaten
by a delusional psychopath
is anyone's idea of a good time.
What you need to do is point me
in the direction
of my heart's desire.
If your information bears fruit,
I'll release you
from these shackles
and furnish on you a finder's
fee of, let's say...
ten percent?
You can propel your finders fee
where the sun don't shine.
Looks like I'm gonna
have to give you
a professional kicking
this time.
Yeah.
But first... breakfast!
Don't get any bright ideas.
I'll be back in two shakes
of a lamb's tail.
Nas is in a taxi
on the way from the airport.
He's here in London, Albert.
Good, so where's the meet?
Well, I can't
take him to Saul's,
so I'm meeting him
in the market.
He'll be here in 20 minutes.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
Come on, big guy,
pick up... pick up.
Hate 'Em, where the hell
have you been?
You match fit?
Vic, now, I'm a little bit
confused here.
What exactly happened?
We got darted, Hate 'Em.
Like wild animals
on the savannah.
They wanted us
out of the picture.
Who wanted us out
of the picture?
Albert, Lily.
Albert and Lily?
Don't be stupid.
Well, it appears
I have indeed
been stupid, Hate 'Em.
Very stupid indeed.
They got used to me
not being around,
Lily all cozied up with Norman,
and Albert wanting
to be top dog.
And... I reckon
they have the gold, Hate 'Em.
Or at least had it.
But I can't prove it.
I don't have all the pieces
of the jigsaw... yet.
So what you're saying now, Vic,
is that we're actually
hunting jigsaw pieces, yeah?
Metaphorically speaking.
So... seeing as how
I can't go after my own son,
we're gonna start with
the weakest link.
An old pal of Albert's.
So, you tidy yourself up.
We're gonna pay a visit
to the upper crust.
I'll make you right, Vic.
Norman.
I just don't get it.
Chair's not broken,
rope's not cut.
Someone must have untied him.
Come off it, Lil.
We tied him to a chair
and locked him in a garden shed.
The man had just broken out
of a high-security prison.
Honestly, I don't know
what we were thinking.
I know, all I'm saying is...
if he'd done it himself,
the chair would be broke
and the rope would be cut.
What does it matter
how he got free, Lily?
Well, he's gone now.
Got only knows where he is.
I will not
have my family estranged
for another 15 years, Norman.
So where is he?
He's not here yet.
Strike that!
He's not too subtle, your mate.
What? Yo! Yo! That's my wallet!
- Whoa.
- Yo! Hey! Hey!
Welcome to London.
I am so sorry, Nas.
Sorry? For what?
First foot on the ground and I'm
into some Oliver Twist shit.
I love this town!
Lovely, shall we
get going, then?
No, business can wait.
Ain't every day I get to visit
my favorite metropolis.
I gotta soak it up.
Hey, man! Yo!
Hey.
Hyuh!
Charlie's residence.
Are you shitting me?
I shit you not.
Check upstairs, mate.
Sweet.
En garde, you cad.
Fah fah fah fah fah fah
fah fah fah fah fah fah fah.
- What's that?
- Music.
Drop the iron and put
your hands where I can see 'em.
Slowly does it.
You're going to be disappointed.
The family coffers
were emptied long ago.
Bequeathed
to various pawnbrokers
by an esteemed line
of forebears.
We're not here
for the silverware, mate.
Then I'm not entirely sure
how I can help you.
I can assure you that
no one will pay my ransom.
Get over here.
You talk too much.
Stay down. Stay!
Now...
where is Charles?
I'm afraid I'm not at liberty
to discuss the whereabouts
of my employers.
I was actually hoping
you'd say that.
Now, where is he?!
Ripe!
Dried fruit!
A challenging nose.
Make yourself comfortable, Vic.
I think this is gonna
take a while.
Stay still! Where is he?
Tell me.
Where is he? Where is he?
Stop it! Where is he?
You hit like a girl, sir.
Bob, what you fail
to understand is
I may well be a girl...
but I'm the meanest girl
on the playground.
And you, heh...
you, you naughty boy.
You've been running round
my playground
causing quite a mess.
Agh.
Where is it?
Where's the gold, Bob?
Teri...
did you know...
Did I know what, Bob?
Did you know...
you can never lose
a homing pigeon?
If your homing pigeon
doesn't come back,
what you've lost...
is a pigeon.
If I so much as hear
your name whispered
in relation to this case again,
I'll find you,
and I will put an end
to the quip that is Bob Fink.
Understood. Sir.
Sling him out.
Aaaah!
Ha ha! Yeah!
This is some authenticated
Brit shit right here!
Ha ha!
Is he taking us
for a ride or what?
Let him get some new duds.
He'll feel a million bucks,
and we'll take him
to Uncle Dean's.
I wanna know what
a million bucks feels like.
You will. Be patient.
Jimmy, Nas Stone.
Nas, Jimmy the Chalk.
Who the what?
What sort of getup
does sir want to be fitted?
Help me out here, brother.
What kind of suit do you want?
Three-button hunting jacket
in an over-check twill tweed,
bold pattern
with the vest and the...
Matching plus fours, sir?
My man!
So, how long is this shit
gonna take to stitch up, Jimmy?
Um... two days, sir.
Two hours, you said?
Two hours, sir.
You're making more friends,
I see, Bob.
You're a curious one, Charlie.
Born into a family of note.
With all the opportunities
that blue blood
coursing through your veins
offers a young man.
Yet you... you choose
to knock about
with a gangster's kid.
And an orphan.
Seems to me you're punching
under your weight, mate.
You haven't got an inkling
of who I am
or what I want to be.
You see, that's
where you're wrong.
I see you very clearly.
'Cause I used to be
walking in your shoes.
Yeah... I, like you,
was seduced by the Hill family.
Extending myself
for crumbs of acceptance.
Wanting to be a part
of the inner circle,
longing, long for a firm
pat on the back.
But let me tell you
from experience,
the simple,
"Well done, Charlie"...
it'll never come.
You're not a Hill.
You never will be.
To Albert, you're just
a posh twat...
who's there to be used
and tossed aside
when your novelty wears thin.
Albert is my friend.
No.
I am your friend.
And I need you
to accept me as such.
Or I will presuppose
you're my enemy.
And if you're my enemy...
well...
Don't you touch me!
What's got into you, Scooter?
What's got into you, boy?
So our guest's been
flirting with you, has he?
Course... breakfast, buddy.
It slipped my mind.
Aaagh!
Dog food, Bob!
Bloody psycho.
Not intruding, am I?
It's your house, Norman.
It's us who's intruding.
Lily, you are always
welcome in this house.
What is it, Norman?
Christ.
I...
I did it for you, Lily.
You and Albert.
What precisely
have you done, Norman?
It was me, Lily.
I untied him, I let Vic go.
Why would you do that?
Lily, you've got to realize
I did this for you.
I couldn't just stand by him,
witness him tear
his family apart, again.
I... I see how he treats you,
what he expects of you,
and I'm meant to just
sit back and watch you,
the most exquisite flower,
wilting with neglect,
poisoned by his selfishness!
Stop, Norm. Just stop it.
The gold is more important
to him than his family.
It always has been,
but you must realize...
- Just... just stop it!
- I... I would never treat you...
All right? Just stop.
Now, I'm gonna have to make this
absolutely clear.
For you, me, Vic, and Albert,
there can't be any confusion.
Vic is my husband,
and I love him unconditionally.
I always have,
and I always will.
Irrespective of what you
might see or think you see,
I know that he
loves me and Albert
more than anything else
in the world.
I know he doesn't always
do the right thing...
and that's what you see or...
perhaps that's... perhaps
that's what you want to see.
But I know Vic, Norm.
I know Vic Hill
that no one else knows.
And that is the man I love.
So what now, Vic?
A kneecapping
or the Spanish Donkey?
Here, I don't know who you are.
But your methods
of information extraction
are nothing in comparison
to when...
as a young lance corporal
in the Middle East,
I spent an uncomfortable week
as a guest...
I don't have time for wartime
reminiscences, old man.
I'm Vic Hill.
I'm sure you've heard of me.
Who?
Vic Hill?
Yes... Vic Hill.
No, doesn't ring a bell.
Tell me where the boy is at,
or the joke is over.
Capisce?
Mr. Hill, I was brought
into this world
without a home and without kin.
After all manner
of foster homes...
a stint in Borstal and a stretch
with the armed services.
The Cavendish-Scotts,
this, unique family
became my adopted family.
Vic, if you don't iron him out,
I will!
Be careful, you bloody
philistines!
Aha, ha ha.
Fink.
Sir?
Sit down.
What happened to you?
Jurisdictional
disagreement, sir.
Dwyer?
I'm sorry, Fink.
This is...
well, it's partly my fault.
Dwyer was complaining.
Other officers muscling in,
chasing leads
above their station.
I told her to handle it.
Sir, I...
You don't have to explain.
I respect a man with ambition.
We've all had to go a little...
off-piste at times
to get a leg up in our careers.
I wouldn't trust a man
who hadn't.
How can I help, sir?
The Flying Squad...
is no cleaner now
than in the bad old days.
A bunch of venal little bullies,
promoted above their station,
and for what?
Because they're better with
their fists than their brains.
No, no. We need an overhaul.
Root and branch.
New leadership.
These leads of yours,
I don't need details,
just...
if they're admissible.
In this case...
it's career-defining.
If I have anything
that could be of use...
you'll be the first
to know, sir.
There is a better version
of us all out there, Fink.
We just have to want to succeed.
This is some
Prince Charles shit right here!
I should run for King!
Nas, we gotta go.
Bag this shit up, Jimmy.
Bucket list complete!
Finally.
Now... where's my gold?
A gypsy camp.
A what?
The best.
Not this time. I said the best.
I want Windrush.
I already tell you.
Windrush is not here.
And I don't believe you.
Now, I have the folding,
and I have the need.
This ain't some sink-estate
leg-breaker bollocks.
This is gangland history
in the making.
The culmination of over a decade
of bile and bitterness.
This is mythology.
And for that,
I require a legend.
So where is he...
and what's the damage?
You think you
come around here...
and use my boys
for this and that.
You never ask him name,
you never shake him hand.
Always you... sneering.
You... flashin' your money.
But you not look men.
You look meat!
But let me tell you
one thing 'bout Windrush.
Him not ask question,
and him not judge nothin'.
But Windrush ain't meat.
All him ask... all him expect
from any boss wanting
the kind of reputation
what you mention...
is a little respect.
Windrush is not here.
Stop!
Not that one, please.
It's the only pressing.
It's all I've got left
of my childhood.
My.
This is you,
your five minutes of fame.
Your X-Factor moment as a cadet.
Alas, "please" isn't amongst
the magic words I'm after.
Bastards.
I don't believe that's
the magic word, either.
The problem with these old 78s
is they're made of shellac.
They shatter like glass.
I drove him back from
the country estate yesterday!
He was more than
a little under the influence.
Blathering on about a...
A golden bathtub!
Complete gibberish!
Golden bathtub?
No, no! And... and something
about gypsies and smelting...
- Gypsies?
- And a girl named Chloe!
Get his car keys.
Give us your car keys.
Prick.
Right...
Got his car keys, Vic.
Where to now?
The Pikeys.
Pikeys. I hate Pikeys.
What the hell is this?
All part of the anglo-rural
experience, Nas.
How are your 5p specials
holding up?
I ain't into
getting shit on my shit.
Shall we get to the business
at hand, gentlemen?
Who're these bastards then?
This is Nas Stone, Uncle Dean.
And what is a Nas Stone then?
I'm a Nas Stone.
What the hell are you?
I am an Uncle Dean, pal.
Jesus, look at
the size of this one.
Aye, man, look at the trousers
hangin' off his ass.
Hey... anything for a favor.
I'd kill you for a tenner.
Nas is our buyer, Uncle Dean.
So that's not stolen then?
No, it ain't stolen!
Hey, get them off my ride!
Rich yank fella in my camp.
Thought I'd seen it all.
So you'll be wanting
your gold, yank?
Or... do you want
to buy a caravan?
Do I look like I'm here
Fresh out the oven.
Horseshoes?
Lucky horseshoes.
It's one way to try
and cancel a curse.
Hold up.
What curse?
Didn't you tell him?
This is deadlier than
a banshee's wail, this pile.
Killed more baddies than
Clint Eastwood, so it has.
Makes Tutankhamen
look like a fairy gobshite.
You'll probably be fine.
They're poking fun.
It's a cultural sign
of affection, Nas.
So you happy with the inventory?
It's all there, as promised.
Let's weigh the shit.
We got scales
in the trunk of the limo.
A sickness of the heart
that only gold can cure.
I thought England
was all Corgis,
Spice Girls, tea and crumpets.
This is some off-the-tour-guide
"Deliverance" shit.
We'll complete the transaction
and get you out of here
as soon as possible.
God damn it! God...
Get off my ride!
Y'all crazy!
Off-the-charts, God damn
fuckin' crazy!
Eeeny, meanie...
miney...
mo.
Whoa...
Aah!
Shit.
What was that?
Where's the gold?
It's in the wheelbarrow.
Fink.
Sh...
Who's this son of a bitch?!
Sure looks like a bastard
copper to me!
Aaah!
Aaaaah!
Aah!!
Tall Paul! Tall Paul!
Agh!
I ain't going out like this.
Not here... now now!
You know who I am?
I designed
the diamond Brooklyn B!
The triple-weave gold dog rope!
I got my shit
placed at Tiffany's!
I got more followers on Insta...
than all you joke shop
sons of bitches.
I am Nas Stone!
Jeweler to the stars!
And I was born...
Shut your mother...
a motherfuckin'...
Grenade! Hey, black man!
Splash!
Sure you can't kill me!
I'm Un...
Jeez!
Give the the Hill kid a sendoff.
Didn't your mummy tell you
not to play with guns?
Right.
Let's go and get our gold.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no...
Albert?
Albert!
What happened?
What happened here?!
What do you mean,
what happened here?
Look around you.
Everyone's dead.
Dead!
Where's my gold, boy?
Where's my gold?!
I lost it.
Me.
Bob Fink's got it.
All of it.
Okay, Charlie.
All or nothing.
Come on!
Fuck!
I'm baaack, Charlie boy!
What...
Yes.
Yeees!
Yeeees! Yeees!
Windrush.
Respect.
Best man gets the spoils.
I can't pretend to be
disappointed, Detective.
That would imply, after all,
an expectation of character.
Sir.
Windrush...
Boss.
So he's what?
Undercover?
Windrush is one of yours?
Don't be silly, Bob.
Private hire.
Been on the books for years.
Very valuable asset.
I take it you're here
to arrest me.
You were supposed
to have been killed
in Vic Hill's lockup
15 years ago.
Often how these
big cases go, Bob.
Sometimes you just keep
plotting away
and get there in the end.
You were in on that?
Like I said...
we all have to go
a little off-piste at times
to get a leg up.
Perhaps if you'd focused on
one thing or another,
you might have made
something out of your life.
But all these grudges, these...
seedy little agendas.
Yeah.
Well.