- Happy New Year, Dad.
- Happy New Year, Albert. Take this.
Albert needs to understand,
if he's gonna play the game,
he needs to go in heavy.
You keep your beak
out of it, Vic Hill.
Come on, Charlie, you know
we need as much cash as we can
to bet on Billy's fight tonight.
I have a very rare fob watch.
I'd like an appraisal
for a sale.
Sonny's got a collection
going out this morning.
- I give you the route.
- Two trucks?
You figure out the best place
to hit the truck.
- We've rung the bell.
- Hell, yeah.
That's gangsta!
Time to hustle, Vic. We'll come
back tomorrow and fill our boots.
One for me, one for the
wife, one for Albert,
and one for luck.
Put it away. No.
Let's see who it is
and have a nice, quiet word.
Get down!
Aah!
- Freeze!
- Stay down!
Bob?
Don't shoot!
You dirty son of a bitch!
Your double-crossed me, Fink!
So, you're telling me
there was two trucks?
Yeah, two exactly the same trucks,
passing me at exactly the same time.
So, which one
did you choose, Charlie?
The one that looked
just like the other one.
Fair play.
Sonny wasn't shipping gold.
So you have no idea
whose gold this is?
Yeah... yeah we do.
It's ours!
And this mountain of auriferous
has gotta be worth
bloody millions.
It's official... we can retire.
Can't retire if you've
never worked, knob head.
Yeah, of course you can.
My father hasn't worked
a day in his life.
Beginning to think
I hadn't been so blessed.
Thank you, God!
- Nobody's retirin'.
- Here we go.
We have stumbled
across a fortune in gold bullion
with no clue what dangerous
bastard it belongs to.
We have zero experience
in trading precious metals,
and if we start making inquiries
to the wrong fence,
we'll come unstuck
quicker than shit
moves through a goose.
No. We stash all of it,
all of it until we know
who and what we're dealing with.
Then what? Suppose
you got a spare safe
knockin' around here?
Shut up.
There are some advantages to
being the son of a bank robber.
Good boy, Smudger,
just stick 'em on the shelf.
Oi. Be careful, sloppy bollocks.
Shit. Sorry.
What are you doin'?
Watchin' them young tarts and
old farts, skinny little pedo?
Some kids posted a video
clip on Instagram.
It's a... security truck
gettin' boosted.
Give us that here.
It's impossible to make
a dishonest livin' these days
without gettin' a camera
shoved in your face.
These mobile devices
have spawned
a generation of grasses.
Hey, Vic, you should
take a look at this, mate.
It's a bullion heist.
- Bullion?
- Yeah.
Here you are. Take a look.
I mean, talk about
a two-pronged attack?
Boom! Opened up that van
like a can of beans.
This giving you
a stiffy, Peters?
Speaking' of pricks...
- You seen it, then?
- Yeah, it's called "viral," Bob.
You goin' after it?
Bob, you're CTF.
Isn't there a shipment of BB guns
that need confiscatin' somewhere?
Listen... Teri.
I know about gold heists.
I did a bit of work
with Flying Squad,
I mean, I... I can help.
Yeah. All right, then, Bob. I'll have
an Americano and an almond croissant.
Right. I think we should move a couple of
ingots for a bit of running about money.
Yeah. We're all a little bit
short, right?
No. Not one single ingot. Right?
No one talks about the gold,
nobody knows about the gold,
nobody even thinks
about the gold.
The gold doesn't exist,
are we clear?
God, you're such a pill
sometimes, Al.
It's Lotti Mott.
- Shit.
Keep your business off text!
We need to talk.
Hello, Sidney?
Mr. Gold?
Sidney, don't get emotional.
Thanks to all this, I've gotta find
someone else for the job today.
Stop, please.
I've always got top results.
Whatever it takes...
I have no complaints
regarding your skills.
In fact, our mutual friend
there is something of a legend,
and that's a compliment
to you, Sidney.
Cost me a pretty penny,
I'll tell ya.
Goes by the name of...
Windrush.
He's the best hired hand
money can buy.
No... no... please, Mr. Gold!
Alas, Sidney, you're
something of a schmuck.
Now I know this because having
decided that no one's gonna notice
if you steal one of my paintings
from the Venice job...
Saul, please... -...you go
and pinch the middle section
of the Whore
of Babylon triptych!
Please, Mr. Gold!
Saul Gold and Associates.
Saul. Vic Hill.
Vic?
How's Her Majesty
treatin' you, then?
Well, I can't grumble, Saul,
and if I did, who'd listen?
So, what can I do you for?
You hear anythin' about the
bullion heist last night?
Forklifts and piggys.
I seen the video.
It's tidy work.
Actually reminded me the sort
of work you might've done.
Anybody ringin' your bell?
Tryin' to move the consignment?
Not a peep.
Why the inquiry?
Well, I'm just sniffin' about.
It gets a bit stale
in here, Saul.
Imagination runs wild.
Well, if you're looking for action, I
might have something to put your way.
I need a couple of cool heads
for a job this afternoon.
Low risk, going rates.
Got a face that fits?
We took a vote. Decided
to pass on your offer.
Yeah, haven't quite reached the armed
robbery phase in our projected careers.
We didn't hit
your boyfriend's truck.
I know you didn't.
So what's with the sit down?
Right place. Right time.
Wrong truck.
Credit where it's due,
you boys are gangsta.
Take another vote,
and then come find me.
Thirty thousand views! This
thing's breaking the Internet!
We're gonna get shot.
Right. I'm gettin' tooled up!
Wait, calm down! Sit down!
Sit down. Sit down.
We're rockin' masks
and boiler suits.
No one can know
it's us, can they?
No.
But what about Lotti Mott?
Listen, I don't know about her.
Do I? I've gotta think about it.
You keep your eye on her, Bill.
I can do that.
- Albert?
- Yeah?
Vic's on the blower.
Well, that is all I need,
isn't it?
We did all right last night,
didn't we, boy?
- Last night?
- The fight, Al.
You got somethin' else
in the hopper, son?
No, you're right, sorry,
I've... I've had a couple
and I'm celebratin'.
Have a tall one for me.
So what's goin' on?
Saul Gold is goin' on.
Saul Gold the fence?
He's called a job on.
Pick up and drop this afternoon.
Ten grand, son,
C.O.D. We will carve it.
Yeah, today's no good.
The job's booked
and it's good readies.
I understand that, but today
is not a good day, Dad.
Every day is a good day
for a bit of graft, Albert.
Yeah, right. Go on, then. Yeah, I'll do it.
For seven and a half, though.
You get two and a half
for the booking.
You negotiatin' with me, son?
This is not a negotiation, Dad.
Six for you,
four for me, chop-chop.
There you are, Mrs. Reid,
your order.
Lily. It looks
just like his favorite shooter.
You've done us proud.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
John'll love it.
Well... would have.
Just finishing up.
Won't be a minute.
Course...
he would've been balls-deep
in all that bullion
hoo-ha, daft sod.
Worth millions, I heard. Every face
in the manor is sniffin' about.
Bunch of prats.
That much gold's nothing but
a travelcard to the coroner.
Or the clink.
Prosperity. Power. Punana.
Sonny? We got company.
You have any... idea
what it is to dance
on the steps of Shangri-la?
"This town is like a great big
pussy, just waitin' to get fucked!"
"Hoo-hah!"
You think all Cubans
are gangsters?
I got my MBA!
I graduated summa cum laude.
I speak five languages.
I was voted
most likely to succeed.
And succeed you have, my friend.
What do you want, Fink?
I wanna talk...
- about a truck...
- A truck?
Sonny, you and I, we got
a good thing goin' here.
This arrangement works well,
I stay in my corner,
- you play in yours...
- Get to the fuckin' point.
Ambitious.
- When and where?
- Five a.m. this morning,
the crossroads behind the strip.
A Donmar truck, a little off-the-books
spot, under the arches.
Anything else come to mind?
Go away, Fink.
I gotta get my... shuffle on.
Our truck takes that route
at 5 a.m. You see somethin'?
I didn't see nothing.
Aah!
Where the fuck is Lotti?
Haven't seen her
since the fight.
Where is that crazy bitch?
Lotti!
I lost my teddy bear.
Can I give you
a hug instead, darling?
Your boss send you
to keep an eye on me?
No, two eyes.
And he ain't my boss.
You always do what Albert says?
When I fancy the job.
I'll get my share of that gold.
One way or another.
Well, I have no idea
what you're talkin' about.
Fancy a ride?
I don't mess around
with the errand boy.
I'll be at the gym
on Upper Street
when you change your mind.
Beautiful. Okay. Lean into me.
That's lovely.
Yes! My angel, that's... Love
it so, that is gorgeous.
Beautiful, now, yes...
We have a situation,
Master Charles.
Father has misplaced
his Volcano vaporizer?
The whereabouts of a certain
gold fob watch.
Gold fob watch?
Lord Cavendish has implied
that I purloined the time piece.
After 30 years of loyal appointment, I
have been impeached, Master Charles!
This century English,
please, Staff!
The bugger thinks
I nicked his blood watch,
and unless it's returned...
he's giving me the boot!
Well... there... there's been a lot of
break-ins, in the neighborhood recently.
Now, I mean, it's obvious
we've been targeted.
I... I... I may know a man
who might known a man
who might know something.
Leave it with me.
Good morning,
Mr. Cavendish-Scott,
how are you?
About that watch I brought in the
other day, I need it returned.
It's no longer in stock.
We sold it.
You sold it?
How much did it go for?
Decent price... book value.
You made out on it, didn't you?
Go on, how much?
Couple of grand?
Five?
Ten?
We had a very keen buyer.
Ten grand? You only gave me
a measly 3,000.
What kind of businesswoman
are you?
Okay, well, can you get it back?
I'll see what I can do.
Okay. Good.
Good. Um...
And I was wondering...
I mean, um...
if you've not got any plans
this evening and...
we could...
- What are you doin' here?
- What are you doing here?
I got a sit down with Saul.
Saul Gold? What's the gig?
You can go on your way.
Go on, you can jog on now.
Yeah, this one's mine.
Okay?
Okay.
You pick up my clients,
the Heimels, from the airport,
and you bring 'em back
directly to me.
That's all.
Couldn't be more simple.
How many Heimels
are we expecting, Mr. Gold?
Enough to wipe your ass
when you shit yourelf, bubbeleh.
Yeah...
Who cares how many?
Just pick 'em up, toss 'em
in the van, bring 'em here.
- And that's worth ten grand?
- On delivery.
What else are we transportin'
other than the Heimels, Mr. Gold?
You're tryin' my patience, boy.
Well, thank you for considerin' us, Mr.
Gold, but with respect,
I'm gonna have
to decline your offer.
If I don't know what I'm transportin',
I cannot guarantee delivery.
You're not like
your old man, are you?
Ol' Vic, he'd be halfway
to Gatwick by now.
Yeah, a lot's changed
since my dad's day, Mr. Gold.
Too many chancers out there lookin'
for a quick score nowadays.
I'm sure you're well aware an armored
truck got rolled, last night,
transport's a risky business.
Diamonds.
A fistful.
Now you in or you out?
- I'm in.
- Splendid.
For 15 grand.
- You guarantee delivery?
- Guaranteed.
Van, driver, out the back.
Piss off.
Left. The left, the left,
the left! Left side of the road.
Pardon. This is my first time
driving in the UK.
- Really?
- Everything's on the wrong bloody side.
You're a Froggy. Frenchman.
Why... Why... Why are you
the driver?
Uncle Saul wanted a family member...
on the mission.
Is that all you got for me,
McLeod? Pig masks and overalls?
Get out!
"Is that all you've got
for me, McLeod?"
Well, I've got something
for you all right, darlin'!
You know, my father said to me,
he said, "Son, it don't matter"
"if you got a two-inch prick,
"just make sure you hold it like
a baseball bat." You what?
It's all right, McLeod,
Dwyer does that to all the boys.
- Makes us feel, well...
- Like dickless twats?
Like dickless twats.
Ooh. Looks painful.
The wee shite trapped my hand
in the truck door.
So is Dwyer gonna set up
an identity parade, then?
She hasn't briefed me yet.
Like I told Dwyer, he was wearin'
a pig mask and overalls.
Did he squeal like a pig?
No. He put on a silly,
wee voice, you know...
"No, you bloody well,
don't." Posh, like.
Posh?
So, I take it you got through
customs okay, Mr. Heimel?
You guys must really stand out
in those liveries.
Yeah, I would've gone with something
a little more... incognito.
Where can we have a little fun
around here?
- Um...
- What kind of fun are you referring to?
Mad fun! Dawg.
Well, you can have
all the mad fun you want
once we've dropped you off
at Saul Gold's.
All work and no play
makes Abel a dull boy.
Turn up the music.
You don't have any more
of those by any chance, do you?
Molly loves you, dawg.
And I love Molly, pal.
Where you been hidin',
baby girl?
You're an asshole.
I'm not talkin' to ya.
I was thinkin'...
you were right.
Your cut of the takings.
What's the catch?
No catch.
You earned it.
A truck got heisted last night.
Three banditos, in masks.
Rock and roll.
Truck got hit the exact same
time that our truck went out.
On the exact same route.
Maybe they were goin' after your
truck and hit the wrong one.
You're a smart girl, Lotti.
But are you too smart?
What are you talkin'
about, Sonny?
Tell me you don't know.
I don't know. All right?
Well, if you hear anything...
from around the way...
you let me know.
You'll be the first.
Hello, my love.
Hi, darlin'.
What's wrong?
Mrs. Reid not like the wreath?
No, no, she liked it, all right.
You missin' me, then?
Do you know there's gold
on the street, Vic?
Armored truck heist.
Well, I um...
I did hear a rumor.
Just... got me thinking,
it brought up some feelings.
What kind of feelings?
You don't think
it was your gold, do you?
Sweetheart...
my gold is long gone.
Fifteen years of battles
and bodies have seen to that.
How can you know for sure?
Am I hearin' right?
Year after year you been tellin'
me to get it out of my head.
It's taken me 15 years,
Lily, but I've done just that.
Now, you want me
thinkin' about it again.
What's gotten into you?
That much gold bullion doesn't
crop up on a daily basis
around here, Vic.
It's just... a little bit
close to home, that's all.
Are you saying you want me
to go get it?
No, absolutely not.
Because I am stuck
in here, Lily.
How the fuck...
am I gonna get it?
I don't want you to get it.
You're not listening.
I was just... shaken up by hearing
them moan, all their husbands
sniffing about for it.
Which husbands?
- Who's sniffin'?
- God, Vic,
that's not the point.
It doesn't matter who it was.
I want names.
For once can you just
let me talk
without making it about you.
Domestic, Vic?
I'll take that as a yes, then.
He's in there, love.
You really this broke?
Or you workin'
the "hot struggling fighter"
"livin' in this closet" angle?
I didn't think you messed
around with the help.
Who says I'm messin' around?
Charlie, look at your eyes.
What have you done?
- Life is a rocky road, Motek.
- Is it?
You gotta loosen up your shit.
Boobies!
Don't pull over, Serge.
Pull over or I paint the dash.
I'm pulling over.
You got punked, pussy.
I'll keep an eye on them, Al.
Charlie! Charlie, come here!
Sorry, boys.
Saul!
Yeah? Peachy, Mr. Gold,
we'll be with you very shortly.
Not you, kid.
Mr. Heimel, I'm going to have to insist
we get back on the road immediately.
Mr. Gold is waiting for us.
What is your rush, Albert?
We're just... blowing off
a little steam!
Charlie, come here.
Charlie, get up!
Charlie...
Excuse me... Can you help
me get these lunatics
out of here now!
Have I... Have I ever told you
I love you!
- Ey?
- I do. I mean, sometimes
you can be a bit
of a crashing bore,
and you have a tendency of being
a little bit controlling.
I... I really do have
very deep feelings for you...
Shut up, come on, sit down there.
Sit down, sit down.
Come on, Billy, come on, Billy.
Come on, Billy,
answer the phone.
Shit!
Hey, Boo! What's your sign?
Get out
before I call the bouncer!
I got money to burn, baby girl.
Piss off, kid.
Would a kid have these?
Get comfortable.
I'll be right back, baby boy.
- Hello?
- Manny.
- Yeah?
- I've got something for you.
Tell Sonny there's
diamonds on the scene.
- Mr. Gold?
- Where are my diamonds?
Where the hell are you?
We're just stick in a bit
of traffic at the minute,
we're on the way
back into town now.
We won't be long, all right?
- Albert...
- I'll call you soon.
Albert Hill!
Fuck me!
Shit.
Bomb Squad! Tryin' to get
you outside the back door!
Don't shoot!
Allez encule!
Bad dream! Bad dream!
Where is my Schmeckel?
And where is my diamonds?
Schmeckel!
Go after them!
They shot the tires out!
They got the pouch!
- What pouch?
- The bloody stones!
- The diamonds?
- Yes, the bloody diamonds!
They've got the diamonds?
How did they get the diamonds?
I thought he had the diamonds!
Yes, the diamonds, you-
- I don't fucking believe this!
Shit!
Who... Who were those guys?
Dropping pills... in a strip club...
with a bag of diamonds!
Might as well have put out
an advert, Charlie.
What matters now
is the stones are gone.
Saul... he's gonna
be very pissed.
How are we gonna tell Saul
that we lost his stones?
You can tell him
whatever you want, Motek.
I'll be on my way,
back to Brooklyn.
Hey, not a chance. You are coming
with me to Saul to explain
this whole shit show.
You took the job
of delivering us to Saul.
You didn't do your job.
I'm not taking the fall
for you, Bubba.
I didn't do my job?
I don't remember
a part of this job
where I shoved those Mollys
down your throat!
You need to be
a little bit more decisive
if you're gonna prosper
in this line of work...
Albert.
There you go.
See? You are coming
with me to Saul Gold,
and that is final!
To the airport, or we'll bleed
you out like a chazzer.
It's a pig.
Thanks
for the good times, Bubba.
You ever in Brooklyn,
make sure to look me up.
It's been romantic, dawg.
Ha...
Sorry, Bubba.
Just... just had to be sure.
Peace.
So what now, then?
Lie low in the Costa Del Sol
for a few weeks?
You have got to be shitting me!
Who's heisted my diamonds?
I don't know yet, Mr. Gold.
What do you know, boy?
Are you okay,
Mr. Cavendish-Scott?
I've had better days, Chloe.
And please call me Charlie.
Strip club?
Well, I've got some good news
that might cheer you up, Charlie.
You have
a spare bag of diamonds?
I spoke to the man
who bought your watch.
Mollys?
And can you get it back?
For 20,000 I can.
Motorbike gang?
Twenty grand? I thought
you sold it for 10.
And resold for 20.
Don't kill the messenger,
I can't control
market fluctuation.
Shot my nephew?
I don't have 20,000.
Well...
do you have access to any
other kind of collateral?
Possibly.
Why did I trust the Hill family
with this?
Your old man has always
been a liability, and you...
you done the family
legacy proud.
Mr. Gold, this is on me,
not my dad.
No, no, no. You made a guarantee.
A guarantee is a guarantee.
It's a famiy affair now, boy.
I want my diamonds back in 48 hours,
or I want their market equivalent,
which is 250 grand,
or I will cut off your cock.
I'll put it in a pickle jar.
Do you understand me, boy?
Yeah, I understand you,
Mr. Gold.
I just thought, you know, if I
got loved up with the Heimels,
I could keep an eye on them.
I thought I was doing
the right thing, Al.
You wouldn't know
the right thing if it kicked you
in the bollocks, Charlie.
Well, that's a bit strong, mate.
No, I'll tell you
what's a bit strong...
Saul Gold threatening
to cut my cock off
and stick it in a pickle jar
unless I get him his stones
or 250 grand in 48 hours.
So unless you feel like
cashin' in your trust fund
to bail me out,
how are you gonna help me?
You know I don't
have a bloody trust fund!
So how are you gonna help me?
You gonna invite me in
for a drink?
You wanna get your brains
blown out?
Billy Ayres... hard as nails.
I thought you were leavin'
that prick.
I will... when the time's right.
How about I call you tomorrow?
You can keep two eyes on me
all afternoon.
I'll see what I've got on.
Don't go spending my gold.
No idea what you're talkin'
about, girl.
You ever seen a diamond
as sweet as that?
They're actually sweet, Manny.
I'm gonna make me a crown
outta these.
You see, Albert Hill
didn't know what hit him, boss.
You did good, man.
Put 'em in the safe.
Gotcha.
Well, this is intriguing.
Back alleys
and illicit meetings.
What have you got
for me, Charlie?
What are you doing?
My God.
My God!
Where did you get these?
If I told you,
I'd have to kill you.
What do you want me
to do with them?
Sell them,
and get me back my watch.
Gold's at a premium right now, I should be
able to get you an excellent valuation.
- Yeah, one small hitch.
- Go on.
They're stolen.
Most likely more than once.
So be very careful
who you solicit.
And here I thought you guys were just
a couple of small-time hustlers.
Does Albert know about this?
Well, I'm growing the operation.
Yeah. Big things ahead.
And if you play this right,
there might be a lot more
where that came from.
Posh.
Happy New Year, Dad.
Take this.
Lucky charm.
Fuck.
Dad's gold.