What's the skinny
on the truck heist?
The street went
dark on that one.
Bob Fink was here yesterday.
He didn't find the gold though.
I moved it to Father John's.
So, what's the price to keep
my commodity safe and sound?
That depends on the value
of the commodity.
I need something, um...
unexpected.
- A bathtub.
- A solid gold bathtub.
- So, can you do it? Make a gold bathtub?
- I'll give it a crack.
Albert Hill!
You've been a naughty boy!
Lily Hill, I am arresting you on
possessing prohibited weapons.
- We need to get out of town.
- My family's place
in the country.
I hope it's comfy, Charlie,
'cause we might
be there a while.
When the gold free-for-all was
declared in the summer of '01,
everyone knew it was gonna
get a little naughty.
Oi, love, move out the way!
But no one was prepared for the
rank slaughter that followed.
It played out like
a gangland's who's who
kicking off
with the Topper Clan.
But the gold wouldn't
keep quiet.
And the Worthington Crew
heard the whispers.
And by the time
the leaves started falling,
so did the Toppers.
Jury's still out on who ironed
out the Worthington Crew.
Maybe the Harriston Yardies.
Maybe the Maripole Ladies.
Makes no once
who did what and when?
They're all history now.
The gold changed hands
over a dozen times
as whole gangs
were wiped from the map.
All for a lump of metal.
No!
Although I've never known
a curse that could out-muscle
that most basic
of all human instincts...
greed.
Does he have the stones,
the diamonds?
Where are you
taking the diamonds?!
Wow.
Cousin Monty was a pimp!
Well, actually,
an Earl to be precise.
If your Cousin is an Earl,
what does that make you?
Well, nothing more
than the cousin of an Earl.
Your money or your life, scum!
Shit.
God!
This is spectacular, Charlie.
Would you like a tour, Chloe?
I'd love one.
Oi, Charlie boy!
Where's the booze?
Yeah, the...
Head east through the parlor.
The wine cellar is through an
oak door down some stairs.
Pick a full-bodied red.
The dustier
the bottle the better.
Got it, mate.
Are you not forgetting
something?!
Like a 10 million pound gold
bathtub in the back of the van!
312!
Cell 313!
Death, taxes, and count.
The only certainties in life.
And I intend to defy all three.
Cell 314?
We're right here, Screw,
exactly where you left us.
Piece of shit.
- What now?
- Go and have a fag.
Spread the word, Hate 'Em.
The Mad Hatters Tea Party
will commence tomorrow.
We'll take the whole wing down
the rabbit hole, Vic.
Who'd shoot a clergyman?
Father John wasn't
exactly a saint.
Gotta rap sheet longer
than the New Testament.
Witness says they were
negotiating
with a bunch of sheikhs over
what looked like a gold bath.
A gold bath?
Anything else?
Yeah, he's given us a name.
Bob Fink.
Mrs. Hill, possessing an
unlicensed firearm
is a very serious offense.
So is planting evidence.
I'll be taking my phone call now
if you don't mind.
Come on, Lil,
have a look around.
There's no mics, no cameras.
Just a chat.
I can make all of this go away.
You can make
a fake charge go away?
Forgive me
while I hold the applause.
Have you any idea
just how much shit
your boy and his mates are in?
I mean, there's enough naughty
on this list
to give Santa a stroke.
He goes away, it'll make
his old man's stretch
look like a weekend in Margate!
All I want is
a word with Albert.
Straighten up this mess.
Do a deal.
Keep everyone happy.
Can't you see I'm trying
to throw you a line here?
I want my phone call.
Call your boy.
I'm calling my lawyer.
I'll give you some more time
to consider my proposition.
And finally,
this is the master bedroom.
Charlie...
This is beautiful.
Yeah, well...
Sleep here if you like.
No...
No, I really couldn't.
Could I?
- Call shotgun.
- Shotgun!
Wow.
Yeah, well, I'm,
I'm gonna go to...
light the fire.
Come down to the library when
you've... finished spinning.
Tell you what, I could get used
to this, Charlie.
Certainly in no rush to leave.
Well, it's too hot to go home
now anyway, isn't it?
Yeah, well, it's been
a rough week.
I say we get absolutely
hammered.
Whoa!
Think we can help with that.
Whoo!
- Cheers.
Fun and games today, boys?!
Fun and games, today!
Matinee movie, Hate 'Em?!
Special features, chaps.
And you don't want to miss it.
Hey.
Someone's messing
with the tea, over there.
In the office now.
He's put some shit in there,
I don't know what.
Sounds like they
spiked the tea urns.
Check the damn milk.
All inmates!
Return to your cells
immediately!
I repeat, all inmates return
to your cells immediately!
I need a coffee.
Yeah, I need two coffees.
I'm starving.
Yeah, Charlie, where's the food?
There is no food.
I told you, no one's been
here in over two years.
All right, keep your
toys in your pram.
Is there a market nearby?
Nearest village is...
About two miles away.
- Fancy a drive?
- I could do with some air.
Yeah, you can take
Cousin Monty's car.
It's in the barn.
Cousin Monty
- really is a pimp!
- Yes, he is.
So, seeing as we are both
in this together,
maybe we should get to know
each other a little.
What, ask a few questions
and then we get
friendship bracelets?
Do me a favor.
You smoke?
See, you're getting
to know me already.
Alright, I'll play.
What's a pretty girl
from New York
doing working
for a fence like Saul Gold?
Well, I went
traveling for a year.
I always wanted to go to London.
So, I ended up waitressing
at a coffee shop to pay my way.
Saul walked in.
Took a flyer off
the counter on anger management
and offered me a job.
Said he was doing one good
deed a day.
Adventure comes to the
adventurous, right?
So, I took him up on his offer.
What's the real story, ay?
We're out of wood.
We need to go
and chop some logs.
Chop some logs?
How do we do that?
With an ax, you idiot.
Who you calling an idiot?
Well, there is only
one person here
who doesn't know
how to chop logs.
Have I done something
to offend you, Charlie?
Do you know how to chop logs?
Yeah, with an ax... you idiot.
I had a very normal life.
Decent parents,
did well at school.
Never wanted for
anything really.
It was a middle class life
with no real struggles at all.
Ooh, sounds really boring.
It was boring beyond belief.
I hated my life.
It was like a slow death.
And what do your parents think
about you working for a fence?
They think
I'm studying accounting
at the London School
of Economics.
I forged my graduation
certificate
and sent it home last month.
You're alright, Chloe Koen.
So, what are we gonna
do about this gold bath?
That was a bright
idea wasn't it.
Actually, it was
a very good idea.
Just not one your bird's had.
Well, first of all, Charlie,
she ain't my bird.
And secondly, she's the one
who put us onto the gold
in the first place.
Actually, technically,
she put us onto
Sonny Castillo's truck.
We happened upon that gold.
And forget who has
and hasn't done what.
We gotta think about what
we're gonna do with it now.
Yeah, what are we gonna
do now, Maestro?
Hole up in the country
and set up a commune?
I'm thinking on my
feet here, aren't I?
More like sleeping on your feet.
What has gotten into you?
He thinks you're
putting moves on her.
Putting the moves on who?
Chloe.
I am not putting
the moves on Chloe!
So what's the deal with
you and Albert then?
Me and Albert?!
Nothing, it is just business.
You want to bang him.
I do not want to bang him.
I can see what's going on.
Hushed conversations,
cuddles on the sofa.
You put your arm around her.
Tread carefully.
The posh one's got
a hard-on for you.
Charlie?
You are properly
paranoid here, Charlie.
He... he's probably obsessed.
I'm not obsessed!
I'm in love!
No, he...
he's just really so sweet.
Charlie!
You've known the girl
for five minutes!
There is no time,
space or motion
in the matter of the heart!
But not that you would know
that, Billy,
'cause yours is carved
out of solid oak.
You're damn straight.
Ain't nothing in those
fairy tales for me, mate.
You couldn't leave this one
alone, could you?
- Me?
- What chance would I have anyway?
When Albert Hill rode into town
on his stallion...
With his spurs jangling
and his six shooter glistening
in the high sun.
Just this one time!
Just one bloody time.
Charlie?
Charlie!
I want my bloody phone call!
Who's that one?
Lily Hill.
- Vic Hill's wife.
- Yeah.
Bob Fink brought her in.
Fink brought her in?
On what charge?
Possession of illegal firearms.
Left her in there all night.
- He charge her yet?
- Not yet.
What was all that about?
What, are we still 14
fighting over girls?
What you asking me for?
Apparently I've got
a heart of wooden oak.
Something bothering
you too, now, is it?
Well...
This whole thing has been one
cock up to the next,
ain't it, really?
Okay, so this
is all my fault, is it?
Losing the fight?
The Castillo heist.
Father John getting ironed out.
Bob Fink coming after us.
The gold bath tub.
Listen, I apologize if my efforts
haven't quite gone to plan.
But I haven't seen you trying to get
us ahead over the years, Billy.
In case you want to know,
I look after everyone.
Well, maybe I don't
want to get ahead.
Maybe I'm alright where I am.
Billy, you live in a closet.
What's your excuse? You're a talented
fighter and you don't even train.
You could have a run
at going pro.
And who says I want
a run at going pro?
That was always your idea.
Yeah, well, one of us has got
to be ambitious, haven't we?
That's not what this
is about, Al.
What it is about then, Billy,
ay, tell me?
It's about you and your
old man, always has been.
You trying to prove
to him and everyone else
that you can get one up on him.
That you can live up
to the Hill name.
My old man's got
nothing to do with this.
Come on, Al.
Heisting an armored
truck with a forklift?
Ooh, that's straight
out of Vic Hill's handbook.
Boiler suits? JCB's Masks?
That's Vic Hill 2.0.
You might wanna take a look
in the mirror... mate.
Dailies, boys!
As Hate 'Em said,
it's gonna be a mindbender.
What's the problem here, gents?
What's the problem?
Hoochin' the tea, you scumbag.
Hoochin' what tea?
What you talkin' about?
Come on, come here, you!
Get off me!
Come on, stop struggling.
Like he said boys,
Crossword's a mindbender.
And you don't wanna miss it.
- All in.
Hill! Get in there!
Full lockdown.
Haven't had
my morning cuppa yet.
Your scheme to mass medicate
the wing
has been brought
to my attention.
I haven't a clue what you're
jabbering on about.
A little bird whispered
the milk's off.
Where is that filthy
midnight grass?
I'll fuckin' shit him!
You won't see him again.
Transferred for loyal service.
Dump the whole lot, lads!
Oi! No morning tea?
That's a breach of our human
rights, wouldn't you say?
Now both of you,
back in your kennel.
I want my brew,
and I want my paper now.
Now!
I do believe this prisoner's
become unruly.
Never too early for a screw
bashing, now, is it, Screw, ay?
Oi, Vic, you don't wanna
go back in the hole.
These two were set
to boil up the wing!
A kicking's
the least they deserve.
You behave yourself.
Listen...
We need them out of here
quick and quiet.
We don't want them
stirring up the mob.
Stick 'em over in Barmy Wing.
Spot of potion and they're
someone else's problem.
I ain't going back to Loony bin.
I ain't going back to Loony bin,
no way, no way, no way!
Vic! Vic!
- I'll kill you.
- Everyone take 'em out! Out!
Take 'em to the Barmy wing!
Mr. Hill, you were due
to be out soon.
But now you're due to receive
another 18 months
for assaulting
a member of the prison staff.
Why jeopardize your release?
Screw deserved more than he got.
But surely you want
to get out of here?
Yeah, and miss
all this good fun?
So, Henry, um,
looking at your folder...
It's "Hate 'Em."
Hate 'Em All Henry.
Do you have reservations for
what life holds on the outside?
I've been locked up
for 15 years.
I wouldn't know where to get
a reservation.
Anger management issues.
Aggressive and violent
tendencies.
When did it start, Henry?
Have It All, what... Hate All...
Hate 'Em All.
Shut up.
Are you scared, Vic?
Scared what those expectations
might be?
As a husband... as a father?
Terrified.
I miss my birds.
I need you
to speak to the Guv'nor
and ask him to give me
my birds back.
What, what birds exactly are,
are you talking about?
Well, Mr. Hill,
so far as I can gauge,
you've experienced
extreme anxiety
relating to your
imminent release.
We call it gate fever.
Sounds contagious.
And you use humor
to deflect the anxiety,
particularly relating
to the expectations
put upon you
by your wife and son.
I'm Vic Hill.
I've had my fair
share of hard knocks.
I've been down on the mat more
times than I can count,
but I have never been licked
by expectations.
What birds?
What you mean what birds?
I, I, I think I'm gonna give
you a small dose...
- You what?
- Help!
Mr. Hill, I am going to give
you a small dose...
Give me the drugs,
give me the drugs,
give me the drugs...
Give us them keys.
Are you still there?
No!
Hold still, hold still.
There you go.
You'll be asleep
in about five seconds.
Good night.
Yeah, Hate 'Em All.
And don't forget it.
White chocolate.
My favorite.
Dailies, boys!
Crossword's a mindbender.
Like he said, boys,
crossword's a mindbender.
And you don't wanna miss it.
Let's get ourselves out.
Come on.
Fly!
Fly free, you nutters!
Hey, come here.
Coming through, doctors,
coming through.
Doctors coming through.
Injured officer!
Injured officer.
Injured officer, coming through!
Injured officer,
injured officer.
- Are you all right?
- Injured officer.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, yes.
Wonderful, wonderful.
That's very... yes.
Vic, you drive.
Injured officer,
injured officer.
You did it.
What the hell?
Bloody hooligans.
Scooter?
Scooter?!
Come on, boy.
Where are you, boy?
Scooter?!
Good boy.
What are you doing, ay?
Flying Squad.
Dwyer.
Chief Superintendent Jones.
A horse got out of the paddock
this afternoon, sir.
Vic Hill escaped.
Took a guard hostage
and staged a riot.
Vic Hill...
Well, it's par for the course.
He's as mad as a box of frogs.
Sir, the very man who hijacked
the gold bullion
in the first place is now
walking the pavement
at the precise moment
that same gold bullion
has staged its comeback tour.
Interesting timing,
I'll say you that.
Interesting timing.
It's Vic Bloody Hill.
The gold has been on the
streets for seven days.
And you have
how many leads, exactly?
We don't have a solid lead
as of yet, sir, but...
Then I suggest...
You focus your attention on
finding and locating Hill.
He may be more effective
at locating the gold
than your entire unit, Dwyer.
And Dwyer?
Sir?
Screw this up, and I'll put you
over my knee and take
my pound of flesh.
Understood, sir.
Hello, fellas.
What have got here, then?
Nice touch, good boy.
There's one in there for you,
too, Vic.
Great, thanks.
So, what's the crack now then?
Well, by now they'll think
we're taking you hostage
'cause we made sure the knife
was good and clear
on the cameras.
When you go down to the nick,
tell 'em we played nice,
all right?
Will do. Don't you worry.
I'll spin a nice yarn
for you boys, all right?
Good boy.
And this is just
to make it look real.
Bloody 'ell.
That's twice you clocked me now.
Don't worry,
you'll thank us for it.
Early retirement,
all the trimmings!
What are you doing?
Wrap him up, wrap him up.
It may have all
changed around here, Vic.
Some things never change,
Hate 'Em.
What happened here then?
Probably vandals.
This would never have
happened on our watch.
Lily?!
I could murder a pint now.
Yeah, you read my mind, Dear.
Morning, morning.
Well, hey...!
Let's have him.
Hands up in the air!
This is a robbery!
Afternoon, Alf.
Everything in order?
Vic Hill! Hate 'Em All Henry!
When did you two get out?
About... 37 minutes ago.
I take it not
out the front door?
As a matter of fact, we did.
Through the front door, Alf.
I get you, less said, right.
Okay, drinks.
Thought you wouldn't ask, Alf.
Two pints for me.
Vic, what you having?
Single malt.
The good stuff mind.
All right. No-no-no-no.
This is on the house, gents.
Very kind of you, Alf,
thank you.
So, what's new in the manor?
Yeah, what's not?
Everyone's disappeared.
They're either in the ground
or inside.
What about the crew that
flipped that security truck?
Any word on the metal?
It's a mystery.
Not so much as a whisper.
- Not a whisper.
- No, nothing.
- Quiet as a mouse.
- I thought you two would know.
Nothing to do with us.
You all right, Albert?
Yeah, I'm all right.
It's quite something, isn't it?
You reckon
it'll change anything?
I think what
will change anything?
Selling the gold,
all that money?
Yeah.
We'll be rich.
And that matters does it?
Honestly... I've got no idea.
I've never really had a bean.
Me neither.
There is a simple answer,
though.
Which is?
Well, we sell the gold,
get the money and find out.
That's the most sense
I've heard all day.
Charlie? What's wrong?
Me.
I'm what's wrong.
Do you take me seriously, Chloe?
Of course I take
you seriously, Charlie.
No, I, I mean... in that way?
Well, I... We haven't...
Sorry, that was...
not fair of me to ask.
- Boss.
- Oi.
Lily Hill, what cell is she in?
Well, she's gone, sir.
There's nothing
on the charge sheet.
I had to let her go
this afternoon.
Go where?
Who signed her release?
Flying Squad.
Lily.
You keep an eye out front.
If the plod show up
send me a smoke signal.
Don't you worry, Vic,
I've got you covered.
If I'm not back
in half an hour...
Run free, Lassie.
Run free.
Lily?
Whoo.
Let's eat, guys.
Well?
We didn't cook all this bloody
food for it to go cold.
Okay.
Toast.
Yeah, here's to you
and here's to me.
The very best
that friends can be.
And if we ever disagree...
Well, piss off and here's to me.
Okay.
Well, it's in the most
difficult times
that we learn who
our true friends are.
Whether we've known each other
for ten days...
or ten years.
There's one absolute truth.
Despite all of us feeling
this excruciatingly
painful shit shock
of the last 48 hours.
There's nowhere I'd rather be
then right here,
drinking this really,
really nice wine
at Cousin Monty's...
with all of you.
To friends.
Friends.
Yeah.
To friends.
Friends.
Now tuck in.
Shit!
- What?
- It's my mum.
She's been arrested.
So, you coming or what?
Seems like you and Chloe
got it covered.
I'll stay out the way. Charlie,
we don't have time for this.
- Please get in the van.
- No.
I'm gonna stay here
for a day or two.
Clear the mind.
You're getting
this all wrong, mate.
- Let's go.
- Charlie not coming?
Apparently not.
What are we gonna do
about that thing?
We're gonna take it
back to Uncle Dean.
It's too risky to take
back into town.
Tell the sheikh we're gonna
need a new buyer.
He's gonna have to re-smelt it.
Guinness up.
You gonna eat that or what?
All yours, Hate 'Em.
Lovely.
How'd she leave
without her purse?
Well, there's...
Some unsavory characters out
there, Vic.
None of whom seem
to remember who we are.
Need a place
to hole up, Hate 'Em.
Who do we know
that would welcome us
into their loving embrace?
A bit more vino?
No, thank you, Norm.
That was amazing, thank you.
Don't sound so surprised.
When you've lived on your tod
for as long as I have,
takeaways and TV dinners
lose their appeal.
Anybody in the mix, Norman?
Now, that's a nice
thought Lil, but...
I think that boat's sailed.
Nah...
And to be honest,
I haven't really been looking.
Why not?
Why do you think, Lil?
Norman...
Norman, please don't
look at me like that.
Lily, it's time you knew
how I feel about...
Expecting visitors?
No.
Blimey! What are you doing here?
We broke out.
- You broke out?
- Nice to see you, yeah.
It's good to see you, Vic,
but, you know, I've really...
It's not a very good time.
You sly old fox.
Who you hiding in the boudoir?!
- No, no, it's just...
- Hello? Come on out, darling!