My old man, Vic Hill,
is of the firm belief that
people are born fully fixed.
Some people are born kind,
some people are born evil,
and that he was born
just plain naughty.
Stay where you are!
Put down your weapon!
Off, now!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
He's never known what it's
like to earn a straight living
and never had any
interest in finding out.
He'd rob banks, blow the
shutters off armored trucks,
and have a crack at cracking any
safe that couldn't be cracked.
Happy New Year, Dad.
Happy New Year, Albert.
Looks like I'm
in the doghouse again, son.
Yeah, Mum went to sleep.
I need to tell you
something, Albert,
and I need you to listen
very carefully.
You know when a kid at school has
got something that you really want,
and you spend all your time thinking about
how to get that same thing for yourself,
and you sit there, scratching your
noggin, plotting all the different ways
that you can earn the money to get
that BMX that you want so badly,
and you slave your
little bollocks off every day,
and you just can't seem to squirrel
away enough money to get that bike.
And I really wanted that bike.
Yeah, well, Albert,
there is a way to get it.
You just have to take it!
- Take it?
- Yeah.
You must not get caught.
You make sure that you're super
duper smart and cover your tracks,
because if you do get caught...
the bubbles will go flat
in your pop.
Have the bubbles gone
flat in your pop, Dad?
It seems that way.
Now, you... take this.
It's a lucky charm.
Now, go upstairs
and don't come back down
no matter what you hear.
No tears, son.
You're a Hill,
and Hill's don't cry
over flat pop.
Go.
- Mornin', mate.
- Hello.
You're all right? Yeah, good.
- Morning, Albert.
- Hello, my love.
- How are you?
- Good, love.
Thank you!
Morning, Albert.
Hello, Eddie. It's for you.
- Hello, Mum.
- Morning, Albert.
- Good. Give me those.
- They're all overdue.
Bills don't pay
themselves, Albert.
Yeah, well, don't worry.
I'll sort it.
- Charlie in?
- Since we opened.
So have we gone
artisanal, Charlie boy?
Brahms and List.
A vanilla and cardamom infusion.
Wholesaling at 400% markup
on piss-cheap Serbian vodka.
And you found some tourist stupid enough
to buy all this hipster shite, have ya?
Come on, Charlie,
you know we need
as much cash as we can
to bet on Billy's fight tonight.
Yeah, the mixologist is my second
cousin on the Cavendish Scott side.
Ooh! A deal stamped in blue blood.
That imbues me with confidence.
Yeah, I mean, we could always just flog
it out of the back of a van again,
but that business model hasn't really
worked for us to date, has it, Al?
You know, when
Billy wins tonight,
we can start to leave all this
small-time shit behind us.
I mean, let's face it,
this is not sustainable, is it?
Head down, arms swinging out.
Yeah? All right.
You be a good boy and load all
that into the back of the van,
and I'll see you in a few.
What did your last peon die of?!
All right, Albert?
Morning, Patsy. I was
gonna call you today.
Yeah, well, I thought
I'd save you the bother.
Which way's the wind
blowing, Albert?
I do need a bit more time.
Come on, Patsy, I am good for it.
You know that, don't ya?
Well, I'm starting
to wonder, son.
You been tap-dancing around me quicker
than Fred Astaire on the nose candy.
- Listen, Patsy...
- No.
You listen.
Don't think because you're Vic Hill's
boy, I won't come down on you.
Money's owed,
and money will be paid.
You got until the weekend...
or I take a finger...
and the florist's.
I've always fancied
having me own concession.
All right, mate?
Keep working!
Hands up, all the time!
And a... Yeah! One-two, one-two!
Come in behind that left!
Beauty!
Would you tidy this place up, Billy?
It's a shit hole in here!
Don't remember exactly
inviting you over.
Right, and what are these?
Thought we had an agreement.
No funny business 48 hours
in the lead up to the fight.
Don't worry about it, Al.
I only went three rounds,
you know.
What's up with you?
You know what's up with me.
I told you this fight is important.
We're six unbeaten now.
We win tonight, I might
be able to push things forward,
make some proper money
for a change.
I'm sick of scraping by
hand-to-mouth, Bill.
I'm sick of living on that freezing
cold barge, you living in here.
I'm sorry to break it to ya,
that's every day shit.
So you gonna tell me
what's really going on?
So I'm right on the back foot with
the bills, you know that, don't ya?
I took out a loan against the florist to
cover 'em and now I'm late on the payments.
Who'd you get the money off, Al?
You went to Patsy. Well, listen, when
you're the offspring of Vic Hill
you're not exactly
welcome at the bank!
Well, does your mum know?
She will do when he kicks her door
down, 'cause I ain't paid him back.
And how much do you owe?
- Twenty grand.
- Twenty grand?!
- And counting, unfortunately.
- Jesus.
Anyway, I'm gonna go and do a
bit of business with Charlie.
I'll come grab you
before the fight.
Look after yourself today!
Stay hydrated.
See ya in a bit.
So which one of you Girl Scouts
is game for a little cuddle then?
Lovely lox this, Hate 'Em All.
Where'd you source it?
The Friendly Screw, Vic.
Well, he is a man
one can rely on.
A quality rarely seen
in our line of work these days.
Used to be you knew
who you knew.
Yeah, and stood where
you fucking stood.
Well, you're right,
anyway, look.
What you in the mood for today?
Apple or pear?
I think I'll go with the mix today.
Apples and pears it is then.
- There you are.
- Lovely.
Well, lighten yourself up,
Mrs. H is on the phone.
Fifteen years in the shovel,
and still yet to enjoy
a peaceful bit of breakfast.
I was just telling Hate 'Em
that my greatest achievement
is having you stay married to me
for all these years, Lily.
You got egg
on your chin, Victor.
Be at a loss without ya.
Hello, Mrs. H, yeah?
Hello, handsome.
So, what's the gossip, Lil?
Just everything shipshape
for Johnny Reid's big send-off.
- We make a few quid out of it?
- Hardly.
But all money
is good money, right, love?
Good luck to him
at the pearly gates.
Wonder if St. Peter will take a bung
and let him in, the vicious bastard.
Is that Albert?
I haven't heard from him
in a couple of weeks.
- He's a busy boy.
- Busy with what?
Flogging moonshine?
Busy doing what he can
to keep us above water.
It's not roses
at the minute, Vic.
Albert needs to understand that this
small-time stuff is simply not sustainable.
More chances to get nicked.
If he's gonna play the game,
he needs to go in heavy.
Come on, you were still trying
to find your feet at his age.
Yeah, but I had ambition.
So does Albert, he's managing
Billy's fight career.
He's gotten him a decent
ticket tonight as it happens.
Billy's fighting tonight?
Where's that, then?
You keep your beak
out of it, Vic Hill.
Any chance of a viewing, Lil?
Come on, I could really do
with a good night in.
No, I wasn't planning on going.
I don't like seeing
Billy fighting.
Ooh, you could put on
that red dress I really like,
the one with the low-cut front.
Show 'em all what I'm missing.
Turn it. What's the matter? I'm
trying to have me breakfast.
You daft sod.
I'm only daft for you,
sweetheart.
I'm only daft for you.
Hey, Vic?
Did you know that the robin redbreast is
actually five and 3/4 inches in length?
El Flamingo?
Did you fall off your
rocking horse, Charlie?
Everyone knows this place
is fronted by Sonny Castillo.
And that insane, wannabe Cuban
has a zero tolerance policy
for any liberties of any description
being taken inside his establishment.
It's urban legend, Al.
Sonny Castillo is
a legitimate businessman.
I'm not an accountant, Sonny,
but I can count heads,
and we had a club
full last night.
That was down to me.
We made a deal.
Ten percent of the takings,
and this is not ten percent!
Always with the drama, Lotti.
You need to center
your fire, baby girl.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'll torch this place
to the ground with you in it.
Hey, hey!
You make me wanna salsa.
I swear to God,
you got to have Cuban blood.
Give me what you owe me, you
pig, or I'll leave you so fast.
No one leaves Santiago Castillo.
Now...
You be a good girl.
Go shopping, and buy
yourself something...
transparent to wear tonight.
Okay, baby.
I'll turn some heads.
And now, the distillation process
takes place in stainless steel vats
for over several months.
The, timing
of the distillation is as such...
Oi, what is it with you boys
and your bullshit?
Just pour the shit.
Where's Charlie's cousin? Just always
expected to be dealing with him directly.
He got caught with his dirty, thieving
fingers in the till last night.
Lil' Manny here had a chin-wag with
him, threw him out with the empties.
Well, you know, he was always
the black sheep of the family.
Pour.
You got a good pour.
That smells like shit.
Give me that, Beanie.
Cardamom vanilla.
You've got some bollocks.
Yeah, well, if it's
not to your liking,
we can be on our way, can't we?
Not to my liking? It's inspired.
Inspired?
Well, that's good, right?
How many cases do you have?
Dozen out in the van.
We'll take the lot.
Pay these boys.
Cash works, fellas.
Well, that went
to plan, didn't it?
"Went to plan," you penis?
We were seconds away from getting
the carpet treatment in there.
I just made us two grand. When are
you gonna give me a pat on the back?
When you start adding some
risk-averse value to this operation.
"Risk-averse value"?
I think you might want to reconsider
our chosen line of work, Al.
You know it was never
a choice for me.
Yeah, and I was born with
a silver spoon up my ass, right?
- I didn't say that, Charlie.
- Didn't have to.
I know what you and Billy think.
"Charlie, he's not the offspring of a
bank robber or a bare-knuckle fighter.
No, he couldn't possibly know his
way around "a bit of business."
I don't have time for this now!
We have to concentrate on finding more folding
to put down on Billy's fight tonight!
This ain't gonna cut it, and you
know that mental case, Patsy
is gonna be sharpening his garden
scissors and dreaming of daffodils.
Where you going? Charlie?
Charlie, where you going?
To dip my fingers
in the family coffers,
so you can remain
in possession of all of yours.
You're Albert Hill.
Vic Hill's son, right?
That's right.
Thought you'd have more about you
than flogging rebottled piss water.
But then again...
maybe you're just like all the
other losers in this neighborhood.
And you're fulfilling
your dreams, are you?
Knocking about
with Sonny Castillo?
I haven't even started
to live my dreams, yet, mate.
All right, nobody move a muscle.
Vic, we got three bars here.
Don't do drugs, Albert,
you'll end up in prison.
Drugs are really expensive
in prison.
- Well, I'll bear that in mind, Dad.
- Listen, I've had a think.
Gonna work the odds
on Billy Boy's fight tonight.
- How'd you know about Billy's fight?
- Have him smack the fella
around for three rounds
without putting him away.
The odds are gonna shorten on the
win, so we go in heavy on a loss.
Have Billy catch a cold
in the fourth. Boom.
No, I'm not having
Billy take a fall. No way!
I'm trying to build
something here, Dad.
Okay. I appreciate that...
but it's page one.
When the odds are there to be worked, we
work 'em. Gonna make a packet out of this.
Get back to your winning ways
the next go around.
I've got ten grand stashed with
Clive at the battle cruiser.
Go and grab it,
and put it on the wager.
And since when did you have
ten grand stashed at the pub?
Rainy day readies.
You forget I'm a bank robber?
Get your head straight, son.
Billy goes down in the fourth.
Bollocks!
Dad just called me.
- Did he now?
- Knows about the fight.
Wants Billy to take a fall.
Told me we'd "make
a packet out of it."
- And what did you say?
- What do you think I said?
He didn't give me a chance to say anything,
did he? You know what he gets like.
Your dad sees things
in simple terms, love.
If there's a bulletproof way to turn
over a pound, he'll take it every time.
Well, that equaled out perfectly
for all of us, didn't it?
Don't be too tough on him, love.
I mean, he's just... trying to
stay relevant. "Stay relevant?"
What about me? I'm just trying
to get fucking relevant.
- Language, Albert.
- No, Mum!
We've been up against it
ever since Dad got nicked.
Unpaid bills up to our ears! We
haven't had any help from anyone!
You're still peddling fake designer shirts,
and look at me, I'm still wearing 'em.
Dad put us in this situation in the
first place, and he thinks he can just
call me up and get me to do whatever
he wants whenever he wants.
Was that a statement
or a question, Albert?
'Cause what I see
is a young man,
and he should be making
his own choices.
Yeah.
Hello, Staff.! Good
afternoon, Master Charles.
Are my parents home?
Well, if you mean "parents"
in the biological context,
pertaining to an organism, cell,
or complex molecular structure
that generates
or produces another, then yes,
your "parents" are indeed...
in residence.
Thank you, Staff.
Afternoon, Charlie.
Everything ticking along
all right, old chap?
Head down,
arms swinging, Father.
Good boy.
Do me a favor, would you,
and pop into the bedroom
and remind your mother
that the plumber was called out
to disencumber...
the pipes and not her.
Okay.
TMI. Jesus.
Christ.
Work the odds
a little bit, Alby.
We'll make a packet
out of it, Alby.
Course Billy
goes down in the fourth,
'cause you have to run my life
from inside the nick, don't ya?
He ain't going down. Why does
he go down in the fourth?
He ain't gonna take a dive, you
ain't gonna shorten the odds,
he ain't going down
in the fourth.
Not going down in the...
All right, Albert?
Vic called, said
you'd be dropping by.
And like a rabbit
out of a hat, here I am.
Any thoughts on the fight, son?
Too close to call, Clive.
Good afternoon.
And how may I be of assistance?
Um, S-Saul Gold, please.
Mr. Gold is occupied,
but I'd be more than happy
to help you with any
inquiry you may have.
Inquiry, yeah, I may have...
Right, , yeah, um...
yeah.
Um, I have a very rare,
gold, antique fob watch.
Mint condition.
Been in my family,
the Cavendish-Scotts,
for over four generations.
Um, I'd like an appraisal
for a potential sale.
It's sub-mint, as indicated
here by the wear on the bezel.
The weight of the watch is 100
grams, so mass value is nominal.
Not antique, but placed into
the mid-century modern era.
The fob watch is not a style that
is in vogue in the current market.
So, we could make you a purchase
price offer of 3,000 pounds.
Would that be satisfactory, sir?
Yeah, what? How-how much? Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that-that-that-that's satisfactory.
Pleasure doing business with you, Mr.
Cavendish-Scott.
Go in. Ask her out.
Or call her later? Now? Later?
Too soon?
Too soon.
Billy, I wanna run
something past ya.
It's about the fight.
And what about it?
Well, I've been thinking... you know
if we work the odds on this a bit,
well, you know, we can make a
packet out of it. Work the odds?
I ain't taking a dive, Al.
- Not a chance.
- Listen, Billy.
You know I'd never
ask you to do that.
So what're you asking then?
Take a few slaps
in the first three rounds.
Right, we let the odds lengthen
on you winning,
we lay down our bet, and you poleaxe
this prick in the fourth round.
You want me to do
the rope-a-dope?
I know it's a lot to ask of ya, but I'm
right on the back foot here, ain't I?
I do this...
and our problem goes away?
Like it never happened.
- All right, then.
- Yeah?
What, seriously?!
Well, you know I've never been
shy about taking a few digs, Al.
- Come here.
- Oi, easy there!
Feint! Protect
yourself at all times.
You're lucky!
And what?
Albert Hill!
What's occurring, Blud? This and
that, Tip Top, you know me.
So, is your half-Pikey pal
ready for a proper tear up?
What do you think?
Fighter weighs in at 162 pounds.
You promised us
a "proper ding dong" Tip Top.
We're fighting Castillo's boy.
Keep your head straight, Billy, all right?
Keep your head straight.
I'm comin' for you!
It's fight night!
Come on, Al.
You've wrapped me
three times already.
Yeah, well, these babies
are our ticket to the big time.
- All right, girls?
- There he is.
Where've you been? Getting
your bottom spanked by Staff?
No, raising funds to extract
your broke ass from the gutter.
- Yeah, all right.
- A "little risk-averse value."
Three bags to up the ante.
Three grand? Shit.
Fair play, Charlie Boy.
Fifteen grand, all right?
All of it to go down
on Billy to win in the fourth.
And don't put it down till the
end of round three, we good?
Good as gold.
Oi.
Round four.
- Fourth round.
- Right.
- Hate 'Em?
- Yeah?
- Fight time.
- Fine.
I'll be back for you,
little man.
Keep them custard creams on ice
for me, all right? Yeah, right.
All right, let's get
the old lady on the phone.
Hey.
Sit right here, baby.
- All right, love?
- Hello, beautiful.
You get us some ringside seats?
Well, the Hill name still holds
some sway around here, babe.
Check this out.
Come on!
You're the man! You got this!
Billy Boy!
Okay, let's have some fun!
Center of the ring,
please, boys.
Right. I want a good,
clean fight.
Leave the monkey business
in the zoo.
To your corners.
To your corners!
Boys, can you keep
the noise down?
The fight's about
to start. Sweet.
Listen to me, stick to the
plan, and we're home and dry.
Stick to the plan, all right?
No knockout until
the fourth, yeah?
Right, that's
when he's getting it.
I hope he remembers to go down.
He'll go down.
Go, Billy!
Come on!
Come on, Chepe!
- Referee, he's holding now!
- He's holding!
Referee!
Slow down, Billy Boy.
Have a live wire
in that boy, innit?
Yeah, Billy Boy, you know the script.
You know the script.
Ref! Wake up!
What are you doing in there?!
- I barely touched him.
- Well, touch him less.
Less touching, please.
Touch him, touch him!
- Too early, too early.
- I know, but he's makin' it look good, isn't he?
Nice! Come on!
- No.
What are you doing?
Come on, Billy!
Oi!
After the bell, that.
- Round four, we're done, we're done. We're home dry.
- Sweet, this is it, we're in.
How you feeling?
- Good as gold, Al.
- Yeah?
What action you offering
Billy Ayers in the fourth?
It's a carpet.
Three to one odds.
- Fifteen large.
- Fifteen large?
Do I stutter?
Well, I'll have to go up the totem
pole to get an aye on this one.
I will take your folding,
big bollocks.
- Lovely.
- Nice one.
Fourth round, Bill.
Fourth round, Bill?
Put him on his ass.
- Come on, Billy, you know what to do.
- You got this, Bill.
- Billy!
- No!
No!
What is he doing?!
Billy! Billy! Come on then!
- One.
- Get up.
Two.
Three.
Four.
I need you to get up, Chepe.
Come on, come on!
- Six.
- Are you counting down or what?
- Seven.
- Are you counting there or what?!
Nine.
Move it.
Box!
Shit!
Ref! He's gouging his eye there!
- He gouged his eye!
- He thumbed his eye!
Sit your ass down.
Ho, ho, ho!
Yeah!
- Boom!
- There he is!
- Bye-bye, good night.
- Stay down.
One, two, three, four...
- Billy, stand up!
- Five!
Six.
Seven.
Bill! Get your ass up!
- Eight!
Nine!
No.
Chepe Vago is the winner by TKO!
Son!
Oi! Hey, what's your game now?
Ten seconds, can you count?
Waving off after nine,
what's your problem?
- That's it mate, that's it.
- You're a mug, you're a mug!
Whoo! Whoo!
Let's get out of here.
I mean, he turned us over!
Castillo properly turned us over!
All that money, Billy, gone.
Shit!
We're fucked! Yeah, and not
to mention the small issue
that Vic Hill thinks
he just won a small fortune.
I'm well aware that I'm now 30
grand in the hole to my old man.
Thank you very much, Charlie. Yeah, well, I
say we go back there and lodge a protest.
Let's go back and kick
the shit out of him.
Hey!
All right, boys?
What do you want?
Sonny hustled you guys.
- I think you mean your boyfriend hustled us.
- Soon to be ex-boyfriend.
Time to move along.
Your eye all right, tough guy?
Still in its socket.
You haven't answered
my question.
It was me who turned
El Flamingo from a dive bar
into the hottest
spot around here.
Sonny's been shortchanging me
out of my cut for months.
I want what's mine.
My guess is you want
what's yours.
Thought we could help each other.
Go on.
Sonny's got a collection
going out this morning.
5:00 a.m. A security van picks up this
month's takings from El Flamingo.
I'm talking couple
of hundred grand?
I give you the route, you figure out
the best place to hit the truck.
"Hit the truck"?
And what makes you think we'd be
stupid enough to rob Sonny Castillo?
Maybe the rumors
about you are right.
The apple did fall
far from the tree.
But if you boys
decide to man up...
I'm only 11 digits away.
We've gotta go after him, Al.
I can't just sit on my hands. For once,
I think I actually agree with Billy.
And you think you've got the minerals to
hold up a security van, do you, Charlie?
Actually, yeah, I think I might.
Yeah, well, Sonny Castillo is a
proper nut, and if we get this wrong?
We are bang in trouble, and I'm talkin' "two
in the back of the head" kind of trouble.
What do you think Vic'd do?
We all know what Vic would do!
This entire neighborhood
knows what Vic Hill would do!
Now, you wanna go and do a 20 stretch in
the nick, you go and knock yourself out.
Get inside, boys, come on.
There's no shame
in what happened tonight, Billy.
You had him beat,
and you were robbed.
Bloody robbed.
I'm, sorry about
the towels, Mrs. H.
Don't you worry, love.
You know it's not the first time
I've had to clear up a mess in this house.
Most likely won't be the last.
Albert?
Kitchen.
So I take it you bet on the win.
Yeah, and we would have won
if we hadn't been turned over.
Somebody's always getting turned
over in this game, Albert,
you should know that by now.
Well, I feel like
I'm losing control, right?
Paddlin' upstream, trying to steer
things in the right direction,
and as soon as I feel
like I'm gettin' somewhere...
Everything turns to shit.
Yeah.
Why is it so hard to get ahead?
Why?
Listen.
I know life has dealt you
a tough hand,
but it is what it is,
and we are where we are,
and the only part of it
you can control
is how you react to the
crap that is thrown at you.
So, you can either be a mark,
or make a mark, Albert.
No one can make
that choice for you.
I'm gonna turn in.
Get up, boys.
We're gonna hit that truck.
Two trucks?!
Think, think!
Shit!
Right. Let's be having ya!
No, you bloody well don't!
What's that?
We've rung the bell.
Charlie... can you bring
the van 'round, please, mate?
That's gangsta!