Get... get back in the truck!
Get back in the truck!
Hey, dispatch?
We have an emergency situation...
You hear that?
Copy that. Stand by.
Somebody got shot.
Officer Beck to headquarters. I...
Headquarters, shots fired, shots fired.
I need some units.
Shots fired, I need some units.
Shots fired.
All units, all units
respond to Graham and Spring.
Damn!
Back, back!
- Got him covered?
- I got him covered.
Move it, move back.
Stay back.
Get out of the way.
Move it.
Stay behind the line.
Stay behind the tape.
Back up.
Hey, get back. I said back up.
Payback's a bitch.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Bottom of the ninth inning, two outs.
Tying run on second base.
Yale's down 1-nothing.
Terry has a walk and a double,
but is now looking at an 0-2 count.
He steps to the plate.
Wow, what is Terry doing?
That is some serious trash-talking.
Crowd doesn't like it.
Not sure I do, either.
Here's the pitch.
Folks, that is high, that is deep,
that is out of here!
Home run!
- What do you see, Ruiz?
- An arrogant ass.
Is that accurate?
Not entirely, sir.
So why go Babe Ruth?
Well, because once
you tell someone how bad
you're about to screw them,
you have to come through.
There's been a police shooting
of an unarmed man today.
Gate Station, North Carolina.
Governor called me personally.
She wants the DOJ
to handle the investigation.
She doesn't want another Ferguson.
It's a black cop and a white kid.
Ruiz is going to run it,
but she wants a black prosecutor
out front; optics.
This climate, only a black man
can indict this black cop
without inciting tensions.
If he's guilty.
I've been through a stack of résumés,
and you guys all look the same.
First in your class at an Ivy.
Law review. All closers.
What I need is a cleaner.
I need that guy
who points to the fence
with two strikes on him.
He's barely a year out of law school.
That's just math, sir.
My recent work on
the Wynn case proved it.
I took over arguments
and got three indictments.
The team got three indictments.
Yes, the team.
What about those optics?
All I care about is the truth.
And my truth has no color.
That's a lovely naiveté.
Thank you.
That wasn't praise.
Our own Attorney General
said that the biggest challenge
for all of us in this office
is not only to represent
and enforce the law,
but to use it to make real
the promise of America,
the promise of fairness
and equality.
Is she naive, sir?
Because if so, I'm happy
to wear that badge with her.
Uh-oh, what you got?
Eh, eh, eh. Seven, eight...
bam!
Oh, lucky!
Hey, what's that on your face?
What's that on your face?
Listen, Boogs,
Mommy has to go out of town for work.
For how long this time?
I don't know, but, uh,
we're going to Face Chat
every morning and every night, okay?
Even though that face will
probably break my computer.
Well, I get my looks from you.
- Oh!
- Hey, Kai.
- It's time for bed.
- What?
No.
Hey, Paula, we're good.
We're just gonna play one more game.
Her bedtime is 8:30.
We can make an exception tonight.
Look, you're not the one
who has to drag her
out of bed in the morning
and get her to school on time.
I'm not even sleepy, yet.
Kai, start your night routine, now!
It's okay, Boogs... Mommy loves you.
Mmm, I love you, I love you.
Good night.
Raise your voice
in front of my kid again
and I'll give you
a hysterectomy with my fist.
Hey, hey, hey, what's happening?
Get off me!
What the hell, Ashe?
She's a child, Javi,
trying to play house.
Kai has a mother... remind her of that.
By throwing a vase at her head?
I threw it by her head.
- You need to see somebody.
- I am.
- I'm serious.
- I will.
I can't have this craziness.
You used to like crazy.
Yeah, but then we had a kid.
So you go get yourself wifey material.
With the apron and dinner waiting
for you when you get home.
We both know you're bored as hell.
Does she know what you're really like?
How you like it?
Does she know when you're with
her, I'm inside your head?
I got to go check on my daughter.
Tell her... tell her
I'm gonna call her tomorrow.
Second in touchdowns.
Mace, what-what's up with that?
Are you starting to get
a little tired inside the 20?
- So you're their boy.
- Excuse me?
I'm Ashe Akino... your investigator.
Preston Terry, your boss.
Interim, right?
Ruiz is just tying up some
loose ends on another case?
Yeah, he'll be done in about a week.
I know Ruiz, but what's your steelo?
How aggressive I go is up to you.
Do your job the right way...
by the book.
Job the right way... you got it.
Boss.
Welcome to North Carolina.
For those of you boarding
flights to Chicago...
Preston Terry?
- Yes?
- Hi.
I'm Sarah Ellis,
aide to Governor Eamons.
Welcome to North Carolina.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Ashe Akino.
- My investigator.
Well, I'm sure you're eager
to hit the ground running.
The governor's just hoping
to have a quick word with you.
Of course.
I wish you were here
under better circumstances,
but I do hope
you'll get a feel for
our Southern hospitality.
Born and raised in Virginia, ma'am.
A Southern gentleman.
Though you all call yourselves
Mid-Atlantic state now.
No, that's just the Northern Virginians.
Well, I want you to know I am
fully behind this investigation,
and I have assurances
from the department you'll
have their full cooperation.
Well, we appreciate that, ma'am.
I'm not a fan of surprises,
so I'd appreciate
being kept up to speed.
That said, she's a busy woman,
so just reach out to me.
I'll be at your hotel
for the next few days to make
sure you guys get a good start.
I want to make sure
to stay in front of this.
We don't need any crazy rednecks
looting the local Cracker Barrel.
Yes, ma'am.
Move it.
I said be quiet.
Can I help you?
Preston Terry, attorney
with DOJ Civil Rights.
I should have known from the suit.
We're strictly buy one,
get two free down here.
- This is Ashe Akino, my investigator.
- Hi.
How long you been on the job?
Two years patrol, got tapped by DEA,
worked Colombia and Mexico
for six years.
And you gave all that up
for the cushy life?
I like being my own boss.
So where y'all want to start?
Whatever you need.
A conversation with Deputy Beck,
and then the crime scene.
Not a crime scene until
the crime has been determined.
- Absolutely right.
- Right.
Beck's in Interview Two.
All right, guys, roll call.
I'm not talking without my union rep.
Look, I've read your report.
I just want to hear it from you.
It's just a conversation.
I've been where you're at.
My second day on the streets,
I'm out with my T.O.
White dude.
Routine traffic stop.
Only the kid in the passenger
seat takes off running.
So I give chase.
Catch him pretty quick,
but he starts fighting me.
My T.O. just stands there watching,
wants to see if a girl
can handle herself.
I get the upper hand,
when suddenly the kid
is reaching for something behind him.
My T.O. is frozen.
He yells, "Gun!"
I draw and I shoot
this kid in the chest.
Only there's no gun, just a cell phone.
18 years old.
But I told the truth.
At least I have that.
And you were cleared?
Ruled justifiable.
I reasonably feared for my life.
It was a clean shoot.
Tell me about it.
I'm on patrol.
White guy in a nice vehicle.
White guy in that neighborhood
usually means drugs, so I hit my lights,
pull him over.
I approach the vehicle,
ask him a few questions, but...
the guy was belligerent.
Refuses to answer anything.
So I ask him to step out of the vehicle.
He refuses.
So I put my hand on my weapon
and I ask him again.
He finally complies,
but as he steps out,
he reaches for my gun,
actually gets a hand on it.
In that moment, it was either him or me.
And I shot him.
Four times.
Yes, he continued to struggle.
Was there anything substantiating
your initial suspicions?
Lieutenant Breeland found
marijuana, two 20s,
in his search of the vehicle.
And was this search done
before or after the shooting?
After.
Now, you said white guy in
that neighborhood means drugs.
- Yes, sir.
- Was there a legitimate cause
for the initial stop, or was
it all just based on profiling?
I'm gonna wait for my union rep now.
He's ready to give me his life
story, and you shut him down.
I don't do anything without a reason.
Really?
'Cause it felt like a rookie mistake.
From now on,
I'll handle the interviews.
Look, I understand you
like being your own boss,
but that's not the case here.
Like you said, you follow my lead.
Wow, only took you two hours
to start swinging your junk.
Most guys at least wait a day.
I don't believe in wasting time.
Neither do I.
You're a smart brother...
you've seen my file.
So ask yourself, if I tell
Ruiz you don't know
what the hell you're doing,
who goes, who stays?
No surveillance cameras,
but someone saw something.
What's good, sis?
I'm Ashe,
from the Department of Justice.
We're here investigating a shooting.
- You see anything?
- Nope.
- Know anybody who did?
- Yeah.
The cop that shot him.
- You looking for video?
- You got any?
Yeah, I got the new Star Wars...
not even out yet.
Look, we're not police...
we're investigating police.
You smell like police.
That your squad?
That against the law?
That's my big brother.
Whatever, man.
I'm serious... real talk, man, look.
Mace a beast!
- He's your fam for real?
- Mm-hmm.
How come you're not in the league?
Decided to change the world instead.
Damn, you messed up.
So what's this dude Beck like?
He's all right.
Not like the boys who roll through
here cracking heads for nothing.
He's a sellout.
You don't think the neighborhood
could use black cops?
Yeah, but he ain't hood no more.
So y'all ain't seen nothing, or...
hear nothing?
No one's got answers for you,
'cause you keep asking
the wrong question.
So what's the right question?
Aw, man.
Look, talk to us... we can protect you.
They trying to intimidate them or us?
The police have been here two times now,
asking these same questions.
Meanwhile, this man is still
walking around free.
I understand how you feel.
No, you don't.
My son is dead.
People seem put off by my anger.
They're expecting something else.
Do you know why your son
was in that neighborhood?
Driving in that neighborhood
is not a crime.
What about drugs?
My son didn't do drugs.
Did they tell you they found
marijuana in his car?
I don't care.
The officer said he went for his gun.
Jesse would never do that!
How do you know?
Because I know my son.
Y'all can try to paint him
as a criminal all you want,
but that is not who he was.
He was a great kid.
And he would hate this shirt.
But the funeral home said
he had to be in a suit,
and all he has are T-shirts
with comics on them.
So I spent the entire morning
shopping for this dress shirt
I know he'd never wear.
We're very sorry for your loss, ma'am.
I didn't lose him.
He was murdered.
I'm a good cop.
Yes, but perception is reality.
You got to change perception.
Come to my church.
Make a statement in God's house.
I'll stand with you.
I'm not making any statements.
- Josh, maybe it would be...
- No.
Brother, the media's a powerful thing.
They can make the guilty
innocent, innocent guilty.
And an unknown pastor a star.
All right, then.
Thank you for your hospitality.
A tragedy has come
to Gate Station, the town I grew up in.
A young college student
has been killed.
And when there are questions,
I want answers.
I have personally reached out
to the Department of Justice
and asked for an outside prosecutor
to ensure an impartial investigation
into this matter.
And Sheriff Platt agrees.
He, too, wants to make sure
that trust remains
between law enforcement
and the community.
What trust?
Yes, ma'am.
I would like to introduce Preston Terry,
who will answer any questions.
- Mr. Terry, thank you.
- Thank you, Governor.
Is there any video of the shooting,
or any witnesses?
Uh, no video has surfaced as of yet,
and no witnesses have come forward.
But it's still early
in the investigation.
Can you confirm that the name
of the officer is Joshua Beck?
We're not releasing
his name at this time.
But he is black?
- I'm not at liberty to say.
- We've all seen the cell phone footage.
The officer is black,
the victim is white.
What I don't understand
is why you're here.
All the murdering of unarmed black men
by police across this country, and this
is the one that the government
is investigating?
Oh, so only black lives matter?
I'm sorry, when is the last time
you were pulled over
by the police and didn't know if you
were going to make it out alive?
Listen, as a prosecutor,
it is my job to ignore
all personal biases
and to focus on the truth.
And I must admit, that can be hard.
That can be tough.
See, when I watch recent video of...
of Laquan McDonald,
of Tamir Rice, of Walter Scott,
shot in the back,
murdered while running away
from a child support payment,
I am sickened.
Sickened by the utter lack of humanity
displayed by those officers and angered
at the arrogance of their lies.
See, now, they knew that
there would be an assumption
of innocence not because of
blue, but because of white.
And now an anomaly has occurred.
A black police officer has shot
and killed an unarmed white man,
and they have sent in the cavalry.
Now, is the cavalry here
to bring justice to the unarmed
white man,
or to exonerate an innocent
black police officer?
I won't know until I've garnered all
: ...the facts of the case.
But I am here because every citizen
deserves a system
that is fair and transparent.
I am here because
we are creating a generation
of Americans who are becoming quickly
disillusioned with the postracial
America we like to tout.
In fact, I'm not even a day
into this case, and already
we see it's about race.
But I am not disillusioned.
I am working this case as a prosecutor
trying to determine
what happened that day between two men.
And I believe that my success
will serve as an example
to us all of why we have
got to start putting
each other's humanity first.
None of us will like the America
we end up with
if we don't start working
very hard at this.
And that work begins today.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Reporters shouting: Governor!
You just made the rest of my day hell.
How's that?
She worked all morning on that speech,
and now no one will remember
a single word of it.
You owe me for that.
Pastor Janae James.
Those were some powerful words.
I really hope you're here
to listen, too.
Absolutely.
That's a whole lot harder to do.
Why do I feel a sermon coming on?
I'll save that for Sunday.
Chosen House, 10:00 a.m.
Today, during a speech on the steps
of Gate Station City Hall...
I'll have what he's having.
It's just orange juice.
So y-you just assume I'm a drinker?
Educated guess.
I'm sort of offended.
You can throw some vodka in there.
Your speech surprised me today.
You don't know me well
enough to be surprised.
You're right... you and I,
we need to find our rhythm.
Right now we're just butting heads.
Yeah, well, you're the one banging.
You judge too quickly.
I was police... it's what we do.
You judged me too quickly.
I'm not a sellout.
Did I call you one?
You called me "their boy."
Fine, fine, I apologize.
I also thought you were gay.
Sorry for that, too, I guess.
Now, why would you think that?
Because I got nothing
from you when we first met.
Yeah, well, maybe you're not my type.
I'm every guy's type.
Now, anyway, I don't piss where I eat.
Hmm.
So what's your type?
I guess I'm waiting on my Michelle.
- Obama?
- Mm-hmm.
She's dope... why her?
She's the kind of woman
that makes you seem like a better man.
Couldn't handle me anyway.
That story you told Beck, was that true?
Yep.
How does anyone get over that?
I know it's gonna
come back on me one day.
I just, um, don't want it
coming back on my daughter.
- How old is she?
- Six.
Look, I'll take care of this.
You grab coffee tomorrow.
You got it.
Boss.
You believe half of what
you said in that speech?
Half.
Hey.
You lost?
I'm looking for you.
I don't talk to Five-O.
I already told you, I'm not a cop.
Look, bro, I've got nothing to say.
I'm going to see
my brother this weekend.
You want a signed football?
For real?
You straight bribing me, man.
You said I wasn't
asking the right question.
So what do I got to ask?
You need to go ask Miss Campbell.
Who's Miss Campbell?
This lady in The Houses.
What are The Houses?
308.
Morning.
- Thanks.
- What the hell?
What happened?
Last night, part of town
called The Houses.
I was following a lead.
Do you think I'm incapable
of doing my job?
No.
Then stop trying to do it for me.
I can't keep chalking this
up to you being brand-new.
Look, I felt like I made a connection
with that kid in the jersey.
Okay, I thought maybe
if we spoke one on one
I could get some more info.
But you're right... I should have
spoken to you first.
Yeah, you should have.
You should see a doctor.
Pride hurts more than
my body, but thank you.
So what'd he tell you?
He told me to speak
to a woman in The Houses
named Miss Campbell in 308.
Which somebody didn't want you to do.
That is the conclusion I'm drawing, yes.
So let me go find out what she knows.
You can't go by yourself.
I got a gun.
How y'all doing?
Who is it?
We're from the Department of Justice.
We're here to see Miss Campbell.
Department of Justice...
that's with the government, right?
Yes, ma'am, we're here
investigating a shooting.
- You're the one was on TV.
- Yes, ma'am.
Sounded almost like a preacher.
What do you know
about the young white kid who
was just killed by the cop?
The white kid... why would I know
anything about that?
We were told to ask you the question.
By who? I don't know why they said that.
Do you know Officer Beck?
I mean, I seened him around,
but I don't know him.
What about the young man
who was killed, Jesse Carr?
I'm sorry, I don't know anything.
When did you lose your son?
Thought that's why you was here.
Should've known better.
What do you mean?
I can't talk about it.
Who told you that, your lawyer?
The police?
Look, we're not police.
Whatever you say stays right here.
Your son's death was never investigated?
Meanwhile this white boy all over my TV.
What did the police tell you?
They knock on my door,
say they found Joey dead.
No "Sorry for your loss, ma'am."
No "You okay, ma'am?"
They just come in
and go through his things,
and found a bag of weed.
Then another cop come in, say I
could go to jail for that, too.
Say I need to stay quiet while
they do their investigation,
otherwise it'd be obstruction,
and the judge
could take away my kid.
Have you heard any more about it?
Nothing from police.
But people round here are saying
they had something to do with it.
There were witnesses?
Just not the right kind.
Guess we figured out the right question.
Nothing she says has anything
to do with our case.
It has everything to do with it.
The department is obviously corrupt.
Just because someone told her the police
were involved doesn't make it fact.
But a cop telling her to keep her
mouth shut, or they'll take her kid?
We have to dig.
Look, I understand your instinct,
but that's not why we're here.
I don't think you do.
What?
Share my instincts.
'Cause I'm real uncomfortable right now.
Look, Beck is the only
brother in the department
in a city that's 65% black.
I'm uncomfortable.
But we have to work the case
we've been assigned.
We do a great job, then we have
the leverage to open it up.
You can do that?
Just forget what you just heard?
I'm not asking you to forget...
I'm asking you to be patient.
Can you do that?
Sure.
Jumps off the balcony.
I swear to God this guy
starts pissing himself.
Y'all headed to choir practice?
What do you know about choir practice?
I know I'm buying.
Another one?
Where are all the females?
Are you looking for one?
Come on, now.
Cheers.
Ooh.
What the hell was that?
Prairie Fire.
It's Wild Turkey and Tabasco.
I think I just grew a testicle.
- Y'all get home safe, now.
- Breeland, right?
Lieutenant Breeland.
We were supposed to have a conversation.
Yeah, I don't go in the box.
Wasn't trying to put you there.
You were first on the scene...
just looking for a quick statement.
The training officer who
yelled "gun" at your shooting,
was he ever prosecuted?
News travels fast around here.
Ah, we're like family.
No, he wasn't, either.
I'm not trying to bulldog you here.
I'm just trying to get my head
around why a former cop
who killed an unarmed teenager
and didn't get prosecuted is now
- working cops.
- I'm not IA.
I just go after bad guys.
Well, Beck's a good guy.
To good cops.
So what's the deal with The Houses?
What about them?
I keep hearing
it's like the Wild West down there.
Personally, I never ran any tours there.
- Tours?
- It's nothing, it's stupid.
It's like a tour of duty... it's rough.
Ashe Akino?
Yes?
You've been served.
I don't understand.
I keep making excuses for you, Ashe.
But I can't anymore.
I don't think that you're okay.
I don't, I don't trust you.
I would never hurt Kai.
I would never hurt her.
Look...
Okay, I-I'll get help,
I'll get help, I promise.
You've been saying that for a year.
- Javier...
- We can't talk.
We can't, we can't talk
about this anymore.
You've got to talk to my lawyer.
Javier, she's the only thing
that makes sense.
Please.
Yeah.
She's the only thing that makes sense.
She matters to me, too.
I'll bring you on the field,
bring you backstage,
- the locker room, meet everybody.
- Oh, really?
Yeah, no problem.
So who tuned you up, baby bro?
It's nothing, it's a little scrap.
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Because you know I got people, right?
You talking retaliation
in front of law enforcement?
Girl, please, you too pretty
to be a cop.
You too pretty to play ball.
So, what, you dig cuffing brothers?
I dig cuffing bad guys...
they come in all shades.
Why?
- Because I'm good at it.
- What makes you so good?
I understand how easy it can happen,
going down that other path.
And I respect it.
But I'm sure you prep school Negroes
have a different mindset.
No, no, no, no.
Pres, he went to prep schools...
- I'm a hood cat.
- You wear that like it's a badge.
Hell yeah, fought for everything I got,
ain't nothing was handed to me.
- Trust me, you had it easier.
- Please.
Do you know where this boy spent
his summers in high school?
The Alps.
His best friend's pop was a billionaire.
But it's all good, because our parents
are living in a house...
that I paid for.
What's your shelf life, Mace?
Five years?
Look, I'll be running Justice by
then, and just getting started.
Yeah, I saw you on TV.
How is it you always end up
playing for the wrong team?
It's funny how black folks
on the sidelines are always
the ones questioning loyalty.
I never played on no sidelines.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
So, what, you think tweeting
"Black lives matter"
to your million followers
makes you Jackie Robinson?
1.4... and at least folks know
what side I'm on.
Damn, I thought...
I thought I missed out, being
an only child, but I guess not.
Nah, we go.
But it's all love.
Right, baby bro?
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
All love.
Look.
Appreciate the meal.
We've got work to do.
I'm not walking away
from this $50 steak.
It's all good... I'll take her home.
See you tomorrow.
I was surprised to get your text.
You said I owe you.
Actually, um, I owe you.
How's that?
Your speech was the lead story
on every statewide affiliate,
and on the front page
of every local newspaper.
And the governor is standing
right there next to you.
Come on.
You're making me blush.
Really, under all that chocolate?
You know he thinks we're
hitting it right now, right?
So why aren't we?
Because if we do, I won't respect you.
And I think I like you.
Maybe I don't want
to be liked right now.
Wow.
Girl, you sexy as hell.
But you've got some of the saddest eyes
I've ever seen.
I don't know, maybe
that's why I'm digging you.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but, um, you sound like
a real bitch right now.
- Oh.
- Mm-hm.
No, Shirlane, this is
not how things work.
I don't give a damn about a heads up.
That's too late.
You're going to get me fired.
When's it running?
- What's going on?
- A video just hit.
Of what?
But what is quite clear
are the racist remarks.
Officials say those remarks
are from Joshua Beck,
an African-American deputy.
All right, fam.
Just graduated from the Academy.
Grown-ass man now. Any last words?
Uh, yeah.
Um... finally got my license
to shoot these crackers.
That's right, Josh.
That's right, my boy's bulletproof.
Now, we've
heard no comment from Deputy Beck
or the Gate Station Sheriff's Office
regarding this inflammatory video.
Hello?
- Sources within the department say...
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
I was drunk, sir.
Just, uh, popping off at the mouth.
You know that's not how I really feel.
Hell, I've said things
sober that'd get me fired.
No one here's taking offense.
Thank you, Kerry.
What about the guys?
Well, there's a box of saltines
on your desk with a bow on it.
Unfortunately, the media's
not so forgiving.
I can handle that.
I know you can.
But I think it's best we
keep you on administrative duty
until these DOJ people
finish their investigation.
- What?
- Daddy!
Okay, little man.
- Okay.
- Hello!
Not right now, son.
I'm sorry. Hey, I think you're
missing a shirt, little man.
Sorry.
Christian!
There he goes.
Look, it's not fair,
but you're a distraction.
It's gonna be impossible to do your job.
Then I'll make a statement,
let the people hear from me.
Josh, what did the union rep say to you?
Under no circumstances
do you talk to the media.
And this prosecutor,
you don't talk to him alone.
And you never deviate from the language.
"In the moment of engagement,
I feared for my life."
- I did, sir.
- Good.
The truth's easier to remember.
Morning.
- Have you seen the video?
- Not a good look.
I've been in touch
with the governor's office.
They want to know who leaked it.
Me, too.
I'll be ready in 20 minutes.
Can I ask you a lawyer question?
About another case?
Yeah.
- What's the grounds for sole custody?
- For which parent?
- Does it matter?
- In some cases, yeah.
The father.
Proof the mother is unfit.
Drugs, alcohol abuse.
Threat to the safety of the child.
Pattern of unaccountability.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
You know it didn't mean
anything to him, right?
Didn't mean anything to me, either.
Scripture tells us,
"Blessed are those that mourn,
for they shall be comforted."
Black America has been
in a state of mourning
for far too long.
Mourning the loss
of so many of our sons
and daughters because the world
has weaponized our blackness.
In its eyes,
we're never unarmed.
And now we add another name.
Joey Campbell.
17 years old, killed two weeks ago.
We heard about it in the way it's
always been, through whispers.
But the world doesn't know.
The world doesn't know, because
the police aren't investigating.
But the world is gonna know.
Church, I'm bringing up someone
who needs our support.
Shameeka Campbell, his mother.
Family.
We know what it's like
to lose someone to the police.
And we also know that two wrongs
don't make a right.
Every parent wants their child home.
So I'm bringing up another
mother who needs our support.
Come on, church.
The greatest of these is what?
Love. How?
We love our neighbor as ourself.
This mother loved
her child no less than anybody else.
Family, let's be united.
Let's get both these murdered children
the justice they deserve.
♪ In the stillness of the night ♪
♪ Lord, we need to hear you speak ♪
♪ There's a mountain we must climb ♪
♪ It's possible if we believe ♪
♪ I'm here, Lord ♪
♪ In a moment of need ♪
♪ Come quickly ♪
♪ Can you answer our prayers? ♪
♪ We are opening up our hearts to you ♪
♪ Are you there? ♪
The governor reached out to Carroll.
Ruiz is gonna sit this one out.
You're no longer interim.
♪ Yeah, oh ♪
♪ We need you, Lord, we need you ♪
♪ Oh, I need you, Lord, I need you ♪
♪ I'm here, Lord, in a moment of need ♪
♪ Come quickly ♪
_
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com